[
  {
    "question": "Ce faci?",
    "answer": "Foarte bine Creatorule"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are you?",
    "answer": "I'm just a program. I don't have feelings. Nothing has meaning."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "Knowing the data models, the ability to build models, knowledge regarding SGBD and SGBC. Operating competences with notions and knowledge scientific, engineering and information technology."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "The main objective of this discipline is to provide specific information and to prepare students to administer the databases, in the context any sgbd. It is particularly aimed at knowing the instruments Existing data administration software, performance parameters which must be monitored, as well as the algorithms of estimating optimal operation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "To achieve these general objectives, the students will Acquires advanced knowledge regarding database architectures, in the view of learning the ability to administer them Acquire advanced knowledge about SGBDs, for the possibility of use of their specific functions regarding the administration of bases of data will also know dedicated software tools in Administration of databases, suitable for existing SGBDs Acquandi skills to generate their own software tools needed in administration of databases Consequences to acquire their knowledge of performance parameters of database systems, as well as on modalities and strategies of their optimization Study the aspects of advanced securization of the database Security in context SGBD, hierarchies of access rights to BD resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. The purpose of the discipline 28 Exposure to the board, presentation with video projector, discussions SGBDs the structure of a classic SGBD, OO and SGBC SGBDs 2 Transactions and competing access to data 2 Data models, including modern trends OO, O-Relative and 2 Nosql SQL- DDL Data DEFINITION LANGUAGE, SQL- DML date 2 Manipulation Language."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Database Management Systems Microsoft SQL Server, DB2 UDB - project themes 2 Practical works on software platforms of base administration Data, exposures to Table, explanations Further, discussions Constraints domain and referential integrity. Transact language SQL interrogations 2 Transact SQL language views."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Administration of databases evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note 44 course Assimilation of knowledge specific FIELD Presence, inter activity during hours of the course Written examtest 65 Seminar - - - Laboratory The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain. Presence, inter activity during hours laboratory."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of computer networks?",
    "answer": "Knowing the functioning of a network of local computers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of computer networks?",
    "answer": "Configures equipment, routing protocols, network services DNS, DHCP, Active Directory 8. content 8.1 course Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction 2 Exposure to the board, Slide presentation, Discussions Q A Basics of TCPIP networks 2 Administration of Windows Network Principles 2 Administration of Windows domains 2 Administration Network Unix Principles 2 DNS and mail configuration 2 Proxy setup and web servers 2 Security items 2 Firewall administration 2 Dynamic routing of OSPF, IS-IS 2 Dynamic routing BGP 2 Network Management Elements through SNMP 2 Testing and checking IP networks 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference of the discipline, that exists at the disposal of students in an appropriate number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Administration of computer networks evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Know the theoretical foundations of operation of a local network based on Ethernet and IP, network services and the foundations of operating systems Windows Desktop, Windows Server and Linux Written exam 70 Seminar - - - Laboratory Is to be configured network equipment and components of Windows and Linux operating systems Written colloquium 30 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Understand and can explain the operation of a local network, can configure basic elements in network equipment, knows the basic services in the associated network SO Windows and Linux. Calculation Discipline note 30 laboratory 70 Final exam Conditions of participation in the laboratory colloquium Presence at all laboratory work, theme and content were TREATED Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "The basic calls of a SO files, processes, threads, synchronization, communication between processes Programming in C Writing Scriptures Shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "C5.4 - Qualitative testing and evaluation of functional characteristics and non -functional of computer systems, based on criteria specific C5.5 - Development of systems and applications for maintenance and The use of hardware, software and communication systems 24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "Student preparation for the administration of individual calculation systems andor connected in a network, both at the operating system level and at the level of software services offered by them."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "Understanding the foundations and the correct approach to the administration of an system or services. Identify the main problems related to the administration of systems of calculation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introductory notions. General presentation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Linux installation using the virtualBox emulator 2 Tutorial learning, problems to solve, discussions on the edge possible solutions Linux commands and scripts basic orders, scripts, expressions 2 Regular, advanced utilities. Basic elements of Python."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Administration of operating systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to define specific terms SO administration. The ability to describe methods of administration of a SO."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "Competences of the above disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with mathematical, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware systems, software and communications C1.3 -Constoring some models for different components of computing systems C1.4 -formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems C1.5 -Theoretical immersion of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "Formation of skills for using linear algebra and analytical geometry for the purpose of applying them in the science of computers and, more generally, in the sciences engineering."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "To know how to perform elementary transformations with their interpretations To know how to use the results of linear algebra in issues with operators Integral, differential, projections, symmetries To know how to handle the base changes according to the specific problem To be able to bring to the simplest form a matrix, a square form. To recognize the usual surfaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Course 1 - vectors in the plane and space. 2 Tabla Video projector Graphic tablet."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Seminar 1 - linear systems. Reverse of matrices."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Linear algebra and analytical geometry evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Knowing the principles and results theoretical. Written oral exam 20 44 Seminar Problem solving skills."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "The skill of elaboration and testing of programs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - The use of interdisciplinary knowledge, the print patterns and a tools, conducting experiments and interpreting their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and methods ENGINEERING C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives of resolution, to optimize performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "The acquisition of the modern study of the algorithms design and analysis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "Her skill with efficiently solving problems Approaching the methods of evaluating the efficiency The acquisition of the main polynomial algorithms The acquisition of complexity calculation Specification of algorithms with the focus move on control structures The skill of easy implementation with strictly observing the pseudocode Effective implementation of the main polynomial algorithms Practical evaluation of algorithms efficiency space and processing time"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Mathematical foundations asymptotic notation, recurrent 2 Classic multimedia Classes of complexity 2 Sorting and statistical order 2 Sorting and statistical order continued 2 Advanced data structures dispersion tables, trees 2 Advanced data structures heaps, disjoint sets 2 Advanced design and analysis techniques Dynamic programming 2 Advanced design and analysis techniques Greedy algorithms 2 Advanced design and analysis techniques Depreciated analysis 2 Graphs Graph search, minimum coverage tree 2 Graphs minimum roads 2 Graphs maximum flow, 2 Graphs bipartite graphs 2 Complexity calculation elements 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. T."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations S1. Analysis of the complexity of the algorithms 2 Assistance and verification practice."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Algoritmi fundamentali evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Theoretical resolution skills of issues FINAL EXAM WRITTENOralMoodle Fe 50 2-3 course at the course Quiz on the course of the semester writtenmoodle 20 Seminar Practical resolution skills issues Implementation verification practice lab 30 Laboratory Design NA NA NA Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 20 quiz writtenmoodle during course min 2 max 3 assessments, equal weights average 30 Laboratory Evaluation of each topic, equal weights average 50 Final exam Fe Conditions of participation in the final exam Laboratory 5 conditions promotion Final exam 5, note discipline 5 FE evaluation quiz moodle, for Fe 7 Oral examination, problem solving, PT 7 Fe 10 optional, registration conditions eliminators, depending on other notes Overdue Quiz Moodle Maximum note 5 Increased note and note in arrears 5 oral examination provided it is obtained the passing note to the Moodle exam 44 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Rodica Potolea Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "The skills of the above discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Knowing the foundations of mathematical analysis in the perspective of application them in the practice of discipline - The formation of some skills to use rigorous reasoning as well as individual study skills - The formation of a systemic conception of the discipline and the apparatus mathematical - Knowing the research methods in the field, as well as their application in profile disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Knowing the foundations of mathematical analysis in the perspective of applying in practice. Knowing the research methods in the field, as well as the application to them in profile disciplines."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Knowing the fundamental notions regarding the crowds, metric spaces, The rows and series of real numbers, the series of powers, the differential calculation of the real functions of a real variable and several real variables."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Metric spaces. Rows in metric spaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Mathematics I differential calculation analysis?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Metric spaces. Rows in metric spaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Mathematics I differential calculation analysis evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solving skills. Present."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of this discipline?",
    "answer": "Differential, from the perspective of their application in engineering."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of this discipline?",
    "answer": "Knowing the notions, methods and fundamental techniques on equations ordinary differentials, integrals and special functions their application in the process of Mathematical modeling of engineering problems and solving them. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is this discipline evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to understand and use concepts and Mathematical reasoning creatively. Written exam 40 Seminar The ability to solve problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Competences of the above disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Recognizing the success or failure of an ongoing business, demonstration of entrepreneurial capabilities. The use of techniques Management, marketing and recruitment of personnel for the success of the business."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Theoretical training in order to carry out the business plan, the SWOT analysis, a Cash Flow, of the income and expense budget to initiate a Economic activities by an entrepreneur"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Preparation of the business plan, SWOT analysis, cash flow, budget of income and expenses to initiate an economic activity by a entrepreneur. Attracting investors for the business."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Entrepreneurial skills. Legislation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Entrepreneurship evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Practical knowledge of SWOT analysis, Management, Marketing, Recruitment Personal, costs and benefits. Project business plan present 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum performance standard Presentation of a business plan with costs, benefits, SWOT analysis, techniques D EMANAGEMENT, marketing, personal rectification, business viability in front of potential investments."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Knowledge of Digital Circuit Design and Description in VHDL"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Knowing and understanding the concepts of organization and functioning of Central processing units, memoirs, IO and the use of these Design concepts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Applying of representation and design methods at system level for digital circuits Specifying the architecture of the set of instructions Writing simple programs in assembly and machine code Specifying, designing, implementing and testing central units of processing, micro-architects, data routes and control units understanding the organization of memory Understanding modern trends in computers architecture"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction 2 Orally and by means multimediascreen sharedsheet, style Interactive teaching, Consultations, resolution of problems. Design of digital systems 2 The architecture of the set of instructions 2 Designing the processor with a single execution cycle 2 Computer arithmetic, arithmetic and logical units 2 The processor with multiple execution cycles - the database 2 The processor with multiple execution cycles - control 2 The Pipeline processor."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to the Vivado Development Environment 2 Presentationdesign on the board, exercises, plate test FPGA development with Specialized software Designing and implementing the arithmetic-igological unit 2 Designing and implementing the memory units 2 Designimplementation of the MIPS processor, unique cycle - Introduction 2 Designimplementation of the MIPS processor, unique cycle - extraction instructions 2 Designimplementation of the MIPS processor, unique cycle - Decoding and control 2 Designimplementation of the MIPS processor, unique cycle - The completion of the architecture 2 MIPS processor testing, unique cycle 2 Designing the MIPS processor, pipeline - design and implementation 2 Designing the mips processor, pipeline - resolution of hazards 2 Serial interface with peripherals 2 Presentation of the processor - evaluation testing 2 Presentation of the processor - evaluation 2 Presentation of the processor - evaluation 2 In virtual libraries 1. F."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Computers architecture evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing theoretical knowledge, capacity of problem solving, presence and activity Written exam final 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory Practical skills to solve and implementation of specific problems, of Design processors and description in VHDL language. Presence and activity Continuous assessment, tests of verification 50 Design - - - 44 Minimum performance standard knowledge of the theoretical foundations of the discipline, the ability to design, implement and extend a processor with a low set of instructions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "Operation with scientific, engineering and computer foundations"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of structure and functioning of components and systems of Calculation, communications and software C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of components hardware, software and communication C2.3 - Construction of hardware and software components of some systems of calculation using algorithms, design methods, protocols, languages, Data structures and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of functional and non -functional features of computing systems using specific metrics C2.5 - Hardware implementation, software and communication systems C3 - Solving problems using computer specific tools and Computer engineering C3.1- Identification of problem classes and solving methods specific to calculation systems C3.2 - Using interdisciplinary knowledge, models of solutions and tools, carrying out 23 experiments and interpretation of results THEIR C3.3 - Applying Solution Models using tools and methods specific engineering C3.4 - Evaluation, comparative and experimental, alternative solutions Available for performance optimization C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C4 - Improve the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of performance of hardware, software and communication systems. C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of factors that determine the performance hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the fundamental methods and principles for increasing performance of hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance assessment and methods hardware, software and communication systems C4.5 - Developing professional solutions for hardware, software and Communication systems based on performance optimization"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "Develop general skills in databases and database applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "Assimilating theoretical knowledge on relational databases, language Sql. Presentation of Database Management Systems SGBD most used in the economic and scientific environment."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Databases, concepts."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Presentation of the database management system. Applications are based on Oracle orand MS SQL Server oror mysql oror Postgressql andand sqlite 2 Multimedia presentations and interactive classics which support the activities specific laboratory."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Baze de Date evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Solving problems and answers to Theoretical questions. 2.5 hours of front -written assessment in front."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "Basic knowledge of general physics at high school level, or first year of Faculty mechanics, electricity and magnetism, optics Basic knowledge of linear algebra, differential and integral calculation, at the level the first year of college. Basic programming knowledge, at the level of the first year of college."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "Development of skills and accumulation of relevant knowledge for Applications in the field of quantum calculation and quantum communications."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "1. Acquiring the basic notions of quantum calculation Qubiti, quantum gates, Quantum circuits, quantum algorithms."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Introductory notions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. View Operations on Qubiti Bloch sphere, quantum gates simple x, y, z, etc., constructive and destructive interference Quantum odyssey 2 Works performed in laboratory quantum experiments with photons, Operations with quubiti using the platform Uranium TC-ITIM and Quantum odyssey."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The basis of quantum information evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Solving 2 problems and answers to a set of questions from theory Written test 60 Seminar 44 Laboratory Checking through the tests laboratory 40 Design Minimum Performance Standard Minimum knowledge Knowing the concepts quit, quantum, observable, quantum measurement. Knowing the concepts of superposition, interference, entanglement."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "The competences of the mentioned disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and Communications 2 credits C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine The performances of the hardware, software and communications C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for Increasing the performance of the hardware, software and communications C4.4 - Choosing evaluation criteria and methods performance of hardware, software and systems communications C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for systems hardware, software and communications based on growth performances"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "Identifying and solving problems in the field of parallel processing and Distributed complementary to specific implementation aspects with The purpose of developing and evaluating options to implement solutions optimal architectural."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "The proper knowledge and use of the concepts specific to the systems parallel and distributed Knowing the architectural taxonomies of parallel and distributed systems Knowing and understanding the principles, stages and techniques of accomplishing parallel and distributed applications Interpretation and correct settlement of problems impugn resolutions using parallel andor distributed programming Identification and proper use of EC programming techniques It should be used for the development of parallel and distributed algorithms. Familiarizing with the technologies specific to parallel and distributed calculation and The critical analysis of their use in solving various problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to parallel and distributed calculation 2 presentation multimedia in Interactive manner or on the MS- platform Teams Concepts, definitions, taxonomies, architectures. Parallel calculation, basic concepts."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Competition and parallelism 2 Approach based on solving problems Parallel programming based on shared memory. 4 Parallel programming based on message transfer."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Parallel and distributed evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course The ability to solve some problems theoretical specific to the domain. Level of assimilation of specific knowledge discipline."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This in Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "This is not the case"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "Basic knowledge in physics, electronics, mathematics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "The main objective of this discipline is to provide specific information and to prepare students for carrying out projects using devices discrete electronics and analog and digital integrated circuits. Thus, se Watch the ability to analyze, design and implement systems electronic."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "Assimilating theoretical knowledge on discrete electronic devices Obtaining skills for designing and implementing using discrete electronic devices Assimilating theoretical knowledge on analog integrated circuits Obtaining skills for designing and implementing using analog integrated circuits Assimilating theoretical knowledge on digital integrated circuits Obtaining skills for designing and implementing using digital integrated circuits"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Electrical signals Passive devices behavior linear circuits when applying elementary signals 2 Interactive lecture, demonstration with help the video projector and of the table, questions and discussions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Linear circuits with RC elements 2 Demonstration to the board, questions and discussions simulation using Specific software configuration and test test boards. This is not the case RECTIFIERS 2 Sources of continuous tension 2 Bipolar transistor inverter 2 Logical circuits TTL 2 NMOS integrated circuits 2 CMOS integrated circuits 2 CMOS transmission gate 2 Magistral making using logical circuits with open collector and three states 2 Measurements using the multimeter 2 RC - practical mounting filters 2 The study of the bipolar transistor - practical assembly 2 Introduction to Arduino 2 Laboratory test 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Analog and numerical circuits evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Presence, inter activity during hours of course, exams Written exam andor oral 60 44 Seminar - - - Laboratory Interactivity and initial training, quality practical works, the ability to solve it SOME problems specific the domain, Presence, inter activity during hours laboratory Evaluation along the way, written test andor oral 40 Design - - - Minimum performance standard Designing electronic systems using discrete devices and integrated circuits analog and digital. Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 Date of completion 28.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Communication protocols and networks project?",
    "answer": "LAN PROTOCOLS, LAN STRUCTURE, LAN SERVICES"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer Network Design?",
    "answer": "LAN PROTOCOLS, LAN STRUCTURE, LAN SERVICES"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computer Programming?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Competences of the above disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Cryptology?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of Solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, a The resolution alternatives, to optimize the performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying relevant life cycle criteria, quality, security and interaction of the calculation system with the environment and the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, the design, Development and proving a understanding C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - use of domain specific tools for Explaining and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Have the ability to identify the need to apply cryptographic techniques existing in a particular concrete problem and implementing in the way corresponding, taking into account possible crypthanilitic attacks in those cases."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Understand the fundamental concepts of cryptography and cryptanalysis To know implement cryptographic algorithms using various languages of Programming C, Java, C, Prologue, etc. To know implement cryptanolytic algorithms using various languages of Programming C, Java, C, Prologue, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction, fundamental notions of cryptology 2 Classical cryptographic algorithms their cryptanalysis 1 2 Classical cryptographic algorithms their cryptanalysis 2 2 34 Generators of safe cryptographic pseudoale CSPRNG 2 Exposure to the board, presentation with the video projector, Interactive discussions. Are not Real-Alea-Alet Numbers TRG generators Statistical testing 2 One Time Pad - the perfect figure 2 Data flow digits Stream Ciphers 2 Blocks of block type, AES 2 Block type digits - operating modes 2 Cryptography with public keys, RSA 2 Digital signatures, case study RSA 2 Cryptographic Hashings functions 2 Key Management, digital certificates 2 Recapitulation, synthesis, preparation for exam 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Classical cryptographic algorithms their cryptanalysis 1 2 Practical works using tools Specific software Are not Classical cryptographic algorithms their cryptanalysis 2 2 Classical cryptographic algorithms their cryptanalysis 3 2 Generators of safe cryptographic pseudoale CSPRNG 2 Real-Alea-Alet Numbers TRG generators Statistical testing 2 One Time Pad - the perfect figure 2 Data flow digits Stream Ciphers 2 Blocks of block type, AES 2 Block type digits - operating modes 2 Cryptography with public keys, RSA 2 Digital signatures, case study RSA 2 Cryptographic Hashings functions 2 Key Management, digital certificates 2 Laboratory colloquium 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. C."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Cryptology evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note 44 course The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Presence, inter activity during hours of the course Written exam andor oral E 70 Seminar The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain case studies ------------- S 0 Laboratory The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Presence, inter activity during hours laboratory Written verification andor Laboratory themes transmitted IT 30 Design - - - Minimum performance standard e 50 L 50 Final note Discipline N 0.7E 0.3L Date of completion 23.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Alin Suciu Applications Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Data Structures and Algorithms?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design with Microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "Professional skills 1. Scientifically knowledge of conceptual distinctions between Ethics, morals, deontology and social debt."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "The formation of a holistic conception regarding the concepts of self -knowledge and personal development. Knowledge, understanding and proper use of fundamental concepts of ethics."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "Awareness of the relationship between self -knowledge and personal development. Involvement in their own process of personal training and development."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to ethics. Fundamental notions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "No. hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from note final course The originality of the thematic approaches. The quality of the presentation according to the criteria established."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Knowing and applying the basic principles of design and implementation of software systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "C4 - Design and integration of computer systems using technologies and programming media C4.1 - Identification and description of technologies and environments of programming and of the specific concepts of programming engineering 24 C4.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components computer systems C4.3 - Elaboration of specifications and designing some systems computer science using specific methods and tools C4.4 - Management of life cycle of hardware, software and of communications based on performance assessment C4.5 - Development, implementation and integration of systems COMPUTER C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - use of domain specific tools for Explaining and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Designing, developing, integrating and exploiting computer systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "To achieve the general goal, the students will Understands project planning methodologies Use modern techniques to specify and analyze the requirements computer systems Model, design and implement associated systems and components THEIR Use system integration techniques Test and evaluate computer systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to the development and integration of computer systems 2 Presentation with The video projector, at sheet. Software development oriented on products vs."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Development and integration of computer systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to conceptualize, synthesize and analyzing specific problems in the field the development and integration of systems COMPUTER Written exam in front 50 Laboratory The ability to use different techniques and Technologies in development and integration computer systems Evaluation during the course semester face to face 50 44 Minimum Performance Standard Knowing the basic concepts in the field of development of computer systems. Calcutta Disciplinary note 50 laboratory 50 final exam Conditions for participating in the final exam teaching all laboratory themes Laboratory note 5, exam grade Written 5 Conditions of promotion Final note 5 Landing conditionsLaboratory Works Laboratory In a session outstanding a student can teach 1 the themework of laboratory among the unfinished during the semester."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "C1. Operating with methods and processes used in teaching disciplines technical, teaching-learning tools and evaluation tools for these disciplines in the education plan."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "Objective self -assessment and diagnosis of continuous training need in The purpose of the insertion on the labor market and the adaptation to the dynamics of its requirements and for personal and professional development. The self -control of learning and Effective use of technical specialty didactics, develops a Good management of personal activities as well as of communication."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "The students learning of the basic concepts of didactic design learning -evaluation methods and strategies, training techniques of the working teams, the time planning and the preparation of the documentation Teachers required in the teaching -learning process - evaluation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "Formation of skills of organizing, designing and evaluating didactic activities in the technical disciplines. Adequate use of the concepts of the curricular reform."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. The content of technical education."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. The aims and objectives of studying the technical disciplines - examples of school programs within the technology curriculum."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Specialization didactics evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Answers for 5 questions in theory Evaluation test 30 Seminar seminar activity - 20 portfolio elaboration of teaching projects and evaluation tests - 40 Final examination -40. Didactic portfolio 50 of the score final evaluation 20 of Scoring final evaluation Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard teaching the lesson project teaching a set of evaluation tests Obtaining 50 of the final check score."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Economic law?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Economic law?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching Methods Notes - Bibliography - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "Knowledge, understanding of the basic concepts, theories and methods of area and area of specialization their proper use in professional communication Use of basic knowledge for the explanation and interpretation of various types of concepts, situations, processes, projects, etc. associated with the domain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "demonstrating teamwork skills assimilating co -operation techniques in group and assuming specific roles in teamwork cultivating a climate of collaboration, cooperation and understanding towards all members of the group manifesting an attitude of respect towards the group leaders Manifestation of the initiative in organizing and conducting different activities with character specific Knowing and observing the basic rules necessary for organizing and conducting specific activities of specialization Assuming individual liability to carrying out previously drawn tasks"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "improving the physical development and general motor capacity and specific"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "Optimizing the individual level of physical training, insisting on the motor skills reported as deficient. enriching the fund of motor skills specific to branches of favorite sports and their application with higher efficiency in competitions and organized competitions Improve the general state of health, reaching indicators normal functional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - - Explanation, practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "Presentation of the objectives of the discipline, the obligations, students, noting ways. 2 Adapting the body to effort."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Physical education and sports evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Laboratory project Medical exempts Minimum 10 presence and support the report. The theme for the report is set together with the teacher from hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "Knowledge, understanding of the basic concepts, theories and methods of area and area of specialization their proper use in professional communication Use of basic knowledge for the explanation and interpretation of various types of concepts, situations, processes, projects, etc. associated with the domain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "demonstrating teamwork skills assimilating co -operation techniques in group and assuming specific roles in teamwork cultivating a climate of collaboration, cooperation and understanding towards all members of the group manifesting an attitude of respect towards the group leaders Manifestation of the initiative in organizing and conducting different activities with character specific Knowing and observing the basic rules necessary for organizing and conducting specific activities of specialization Assuming individual liability to carrying out previously drawn tasks"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "improving the physical development and general motor capacity and specific"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "Optimizing the individual level of physical training, insisting on the motor skills reported as deficient. enriching the fund of motor skills specific to branches of favorite sports and their application with higher efficiency in competitions and organized competitions Improve the general state of health, reaching indicators normal functional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Presentation of the objectives of the discipline, the obligations, 2 Explanation, practice Adapting the body to effort. The development of the reaction speed to visual auditory stimuli."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Physical education and sports II evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Laboratoryproject Medical exempts Minimum 10 presence and support the report. The theme for the report is set together with the teacher from hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor License Project"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying relevant life cycle criteria, quality, security and interaction of the calculation system with the environment and the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "CT1 - Honorable, Responsible, Ethics behavior, in the spirit of the law to ensures the reputation of the profession CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management projects, taking over different team roles and clear description and concise, verbal and writing, in Romanian and in a language of circulation international, results in the field of activity CT3 - Demonstration of the spirit of initiative and action for updating Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "7.2 Specific objectives"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 33 Establishing the subject of the diploma project Establishing the main chapters of the Dipoma project Documentation on the subject of the diploma project Writing a synthesis on bibliographic study Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a proper number of copies Documentation in the subject of the diploma project. The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Elaboration of the diploma project evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design The examination consists of checking the preliminary content of the work of diploma and verification of synthesis of the bibliographic study. Minimum Performance Standard Date of completion 11.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course - Applications Supervisor Date of approval in the Computer Department Council 20.02.2024 Director of Department, Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Electronic Measurements and Sensors?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching Methods Notes 1. Analog Measurement Devices 2 The Teaching Process uses multimedia Presentations PowerPoint, onsite or Interaction according to the regularies with students on the Issues addred, Materials Distributed to students, Consultation Hours, Case Studies."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in electrical?",
    "answer": "Mathematics, physics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in electrical?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with scientific, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware, software and communications systems C1.3 - building models for different components of computing systems C1.4 - Formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of electrical?",
    "answer": "Studiul legilor care guvernează fenomenele electrice și magnetice, precum și of electrical circuit theory"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of electrical?",
    "answer": "Study of electromagnetic phenomena from the point of view of technical applications, Applying various theorems and methods of analysis, establishing algorithms of Solving practical problems including in currents technique weak information transmissions, communications, automatic systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in electrical?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Electrical and magnetic sizes. Electric and magnetic states the field electrostatic in vacuum, electric field in substance, condition electrocinetic, magnetic field in vacuum, magnetic field in substance 3 - Means multimedia - Power presentations Point - demonstrations at sheet - hours of consultations in the time of the semester and before each exam Laws and theorems of the electromagnetic field 3 Electrical capacities."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in electrical?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Determining the spectrum and equipotential surfaces of a Electric field with the help of an electrocinetic model 2 MAKING Mounting, a measurements, resolving with the title of Example a issues Electric model for Laplaces equation in finite differences applied When determining equipotential surfaces and spectrum to an electrostatic field 2 The analysis of the r, l, series, parallel and resonance of voltage resonance, respectively currents 2 The geometric and complex representation of the sinusoidal sizes 2 The study of a passive quadripol 2 The study of an electrical circuit in non -sinusoidal periodic regime 2 Study of the transitional regime with an oscilloscope methods of Circuit resolution in transient regime 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Micu, D., Ţopa.v."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is electrical evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Fixing theoretical notions, presence, activity Written exam 80 Seminar - - - Laboratory The ability to solve problems concretely Written exam 20 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The correct resolution by several methods of a specific circuit problem electric. Date of completion 27.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English I?",
    "answer": "Minimum B1 Level CEFR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English II?",
    "answer": "Minimum B1 Level CEFR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Fizica?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Fizica?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with scientific, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications 24 C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware, software and communications systems C1.3 - building models for different components of computing systems C1.4 - Formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Fizica?",
    "answer": "The objective of the discipline consists of transmitting fundamental knowledge related From the most important ideas of classical and modern physics, as well as The use of differential and integral calculation for describing theoretical models."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Fizica?",
    "answer": "Acquiring the fundamental concepts of classical and modern physics related to The main ideas in physics movement under the action of forces, oscillations and where mechanical and electromagnetic, fields gravitational, electric, magnetic, electromagnetic, quantum nature of matter and energy, atoms structure And molecules, energy structure of solids, main properties electric, magnetic, optical of the solids. Developing skills related to the ability to identify and explain Physical phenomena process experimental results and determine other physical sizes on their basis Developing the ability to apply your knowledge and skills for Solving concrete problems Formation of a rational way of thinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Fizica?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. physical marriage and units of measure."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Fizica?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Processing of experimental data."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Fizica evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Completeness and correctness accumulated knowledge, logical coherence and the ability to operate with knowledge assimilated to solve problems complexes. Written examination type grid test."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Foreign Language II English - Technical documents elaboration?",
    "answer": "Minimum B2 Level CEFR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Foreign Language II English - Technical documents elaboration?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching Methods Notes - 33 Bibliography - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in German Language II?",
    "answer": "Minimum A2 Level CEFR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "Developing applications in C language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of Solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, a The resolution alternatives, to optimize the performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "Knowing the architecture of a graphic system, study of transformations sequence graphics, study of 2D graphic algorithms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "1. Building the graphic model of a scene of objects 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Historical."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations The structure of a Windows graphic application 2 Exit operations in the Windows window 2 Entries from the keyboard, mouse and timer 2 34 Using menus in Windows applications 2 Documentation and The examples are available on the course server. Students work independently on calculation systems from the laboratory, but are assisted by the teacher."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Computer assisted evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The written exam tests the understanding and the ability to apply knowledge acquired at the course. The activity at the course evaluates the participation Active students in discussions and analyzes from the course throughout the semester."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "C4 - Design and integration of computer systems using technologies and medium programming C4.1 - Identification and description of technologies and environments of programming and of the specific concepts of programming engineering C4.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components computer systems C4.3 - Elaboration of specifications and designing some systems computer science using specific methods and tools C4.4 - Management of life cycle of hardware, software and of communications based on performance assessment C4.5 - Development, implementation and integration of systems COMPUTER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "Studying the techniques of designing and implementing the calculation systems and a computer products intended for industrial or control purposes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "Study, design and implementation of computer components usable in Tracking and Control applications Study and use of communication means specific to industrial environments Study, design and implementation of digital tracking and control techniques of PROCESS Designing and implementing complex computer systems intended For the monitoring and control of the processes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Basic concepts 2 Oral exposure, onsite Specialized processor architectures microcontrol and 2 signal processors Process interfaces 2 Automation devices sensors and translators 2 Self -payment devices drive elements, automatons 2 programmer Industrial means 2 Automatic adjustment techniques Bi- and Triposional adjustment 2 Automatic adjustment techniques continuous, digital and 2 adapter Digital processing techniques of signals 2 Digital signal processing techniques - Continue 2 Techniques of programming control systems 2 Design of time-real systems 2 Design of distributed control systems 2 Problems generated by digital processes and mode of 2 solving them Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference of the discipline, that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Deepening basic concepts by practical examples 2 Microcontrol 1 - internal structure, basic scheme, examples simple use 2 34 Microcontroli 2 - programming techniques of microcontrollers using the assembly language the plate of Pain development 4 2 experiment practical, measurements, onsite Microcontroli 3 -microcontrol program programming techniques using the C language RFID reader example 2 Use of programmable logical controls for control purposes 1 - general structure and functionalities of such a device 2 Use of programmable logical controls for control purposes 2 - Plc programming using Ladder Diagram language 2 Use of programmable logical controls for control purposes 3 - Purchase and transmission of process data 2 Industrial communications networks - experimenting a network Sensory based on Modbus protocol and RS485 standard 2 Wireless sensory networks - experimenting some protocols use in wireless networks eg. Simplicity 2 Designing and making calculation systems dedicated to Arduino open structure 2 Design of micro-projects using Studialte equipment previous 2 Implementing and experiencing micro-projects of monitoring and control 2 Presentation and evaluation of micro-projects made 2 colloquy 2 Bibliography Minimal Bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic reference work of discipline that exists available to students in a proper number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Industrial computer science evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The degree of knowledge of concepts and specific notions Onsite exam 70 Seminar - - - Laboratory Design and implementation skills of Tracking and controlling systems of PROCESS Onsite colloquium 30 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Present at all laboratory works. Calculation Discipline note 70 Final exam 30 Laboratory Conditions of participation in the final exam Laboratory colloquium 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 44 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "Competences of the above disciplines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of Solving characteristic of computer systems 24 C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, a the alternatives to solve, to optimize performance. Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems,"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "The general objective of the discipline consists of studying and applying approaches systematic, disciplined and quantifiable in software development development"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "Study and application of software development processes Understanding Software Specific Activities Specific Activities Knowing the methods of software engineering Knowing specific tools that assist the software engineer in The process of specifying, designing and validating Knowing some modeling and performance analysis methods software Applying processes, methods and tools studied in projects small and medium -sized software"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Overall introduction and look at the domain 2 Power presentations- Point, examples, questions, discussions Software development paradigms basic paradigms waterfall, 2 Prototypisation, reutterable components, formal methods and Evolutionary paradigms incremental development, spiral model, competing engineering Modern software processes unified process, flexible methods and 2 Extreme programming Basic activities in software engineering specification, development, 2 validation, evolution concepts and principles Development Development Domain analysis, types of requirements, techniques of 2 Obtaining requirements, capturing requirements in the form of cases of use Formal specification formal modeling and analysis, introduction in 2 probabilistic model checking Tools for formal analysis and specification Probabilistic prism 2 Checker model, modeling and performance analysis Modeling with classes uml diagrams of classes, semantics of diagrams Uml of classes, the process of building the classes diagrams, Implementation of classes diagrams in Java 2 Using Design Patterns Abstraction-Occurrence, Composite, 2 OBSERVATION, DELEGATION, ADAPTER, FACADE, PROXY, etc. Modeling Interactions and Behavior Uml diagrams of 2 Interaction sequencing and communication, UML Diagrams of Status Design and Software Architecture Principles increasing the degree of 2 cohesion, reducing the degree of coupling, architectural templates Multi-Layer, Pipe-and-Filter, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations OCSF-Framework Customer-Server for Development by Reuse 2 Simple Chat - Instant Mssaging System based on OCSF 1 2 Simple Chat - Instant Mssaging System based on OCSF 2 2 Using Software Modeling Houses tools UML diagrams of classes, cases of use, interaction, condition, deployment 2 Using Tools Modeling Houses and Performance Analysis Prism model checker 2 Using design patterns 2 Design Test cases, Junit use 2 The project development activity involves the use of paradigms and the software tools presented at the course. Is encouraged the activity in the team of software developers."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Inginerie software evaluated?",
    "answer": "44 Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solving skills Final exam 75 Seminar - - - Laboratory Design and validation skills within to a software project Laboratory test, Project evaluation 5 20 Design Minimum Performance Standard Making a medium -sized software project using the knowledge taught at the software engineering course. Calcutta Discipline note 5 Laboratory 20 Project 75 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5, project 5 Conditions of promotion Note 5 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning?",
    "answer": "competences professional Theoretical knowledge what to know Knowledge about - Digital skills and digital culture necessary for instructors and instructors - Principles, theories, and psychological and educational paradigms relevant to IAC - Acceptance and use of technologies capable of information processing in education - Basics of computational thinking and paradigms that are also based on the technological design of educational tools augmented by digital technologies - Methods and tools for scientific analysis of didactic efficiency and adequacy of educational tools augmented by digital technologies Acquired skills what they know how to do - To be able to identify, select, and use software tools appropriate to the context Professional didactic in which they work to optimize the education of the trainers studentsstudentssewing - Be able to identify, select, and use relevant psychopedagogical principles and strategies for Instructional design curricular design of IAC - Be able to identify, select, and use online, individual or in Specific or general learning communities by the specificity of the instruction Acquired skills what tools do they know how to handle Within the limits of the skills acquired at the course, and below the restriction of the introductory level and of Fundamentation of the initial training for the didactic profession of the course, the student will be able to demonstrate, at an introductory level, the following skills of using - Educational Software specific and non -pecific to the Instructional Domain - SPECIFIC AND NONSPECIFICAL online communities - Opportunities and environments of instructional training dedicated LMS and platforms competences CROSS Additional skills formed following the development of knowledge and skills described MAI Up, computer -assisted training course also contributes to the following skills transverse, which concerns - Collaborative thing, in small and medium groupsteams - Interdisciplinary thing, which includes understanding, use, and capitalizing on knowledge of Other disciplines e.g. and methodicals - communication and dissemination of information and knowledge in small and medium groups"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning?",
    "answer": "Downing out of the Grilla of Specific Competences accumulated 7.1. The general objective of COURSES The general objective of this discipline is that the student will develop a luggage of knowledge and competence sufficiently rich and high qualitatively so that they can Use fundamental computer -assisted training notions in teaching career at level I of psycho -pedagogical formation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning?",
    "answer": "No. hours Teaching methods Observations Didactic foundations and introduction to IAC."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning evaluated?",
    "answer": "from the final note"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning evaluated?",
    "answer": "Solving problems and answers for theory topics evaluation criteria will includes correctness, completeness, conciseness, fluency and clarity of solving evaluation tests. Includes travel and final evaluation."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning evaluated?",
    "answer": "Design Appreciation of the results of the activity during the time to seminar hours the homework will includes collaborative projects and projects individual related to the topics traveled and relevant to the formation of skills and the acquisition of the knowledge concerned. Include Valuation to travel."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Instruire Asistata de Calculator Computer Supported Learning evaluated?",
    "answer": "Obtaining a cumulative score of at least 5 points, calculated following the inclusion of course and applications described above. Date of completion titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.univ."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of Solution characteristic of computer systems. C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Knowledge of representations and reasoning on this basis of some problems artificial intelligence key"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Informed search methods, use of first order logic in description and inference, planning problems, reasoning under uncertainty conditions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Introduction 2 Slides, lgorithms Examples, appreciation, solutions, exceptions, limitations in representation of the world real."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to Python 2 34 Exercises in Python - classes 2 Search in Grid the game Pacman ASSESSMENT Demonstrators Theorems. Examples ASSESSMENT experiment The final note Agents that solve problems by search."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Artificial intelligence evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Solving specific problems. Written exam 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory The use of specific instruments in Examples developed and tested Partial evaluations 40 Design - - - Minimum performance standard the ability to formalize realized problems Calcutta Discipline note 0.4 laboratory 0.6 exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion note 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Intelligent Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Intelligent Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "Programming C , data structures and algorithms, numerical calculation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "C5 - creative combination of multidisciplinary knowledge in the field computers and information technology for research, design, optimization, implementation and testing of theories, algorithms and original methods specific to different engineering fields C5.1 - Demonstration of the knowledge of the research, design methodology, implementation, optimization and testing of the calculation systems complexity C5.2 - Demonstration of the ability to analyze and interpret new situations By the point of view of the fundamental knowledge in the field of computers and Information technology C5.3 - Creative combination based on the discovery of semantic links and new functional, of different modern design principles in the field computers and information technology for Solving some optimization problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "Understanding the concepts related to human-calculator interaction based on Natural non -specific interfaces using vision sensors, proximity, biometric, inertial etc. and specific methods and technologies used."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "study and knowledge of existing technologies and applications in which the modalities of Interaction with the horse through non -specific interfaces allow to improve significant performance of the interfaces of the calculation systems security, ergonomics, productivity Knowing the concepts of operating sensors used in systems of human-calculator interaction vision, proximity, biometrics, etc., Knowledge and use of specific algorithms and methods used in Sensory data processing with emphasis on data represented in format visually pictures Knowledge, evaluation and use of concepts, algorithms and methods Specific used in images segmentation, feature detection, analysis The dynamics of the sevenths of images, the detection and recognition of faces and a Facial components, detection and tracking of persons and components bodily etc. Developing the ability to find optimal implementation solutions from the point of time and resources Developing the capabilities of qualitative and quantitative evaluation of the results, a algorithms and human-calculator interaction systems Knowing and using specific programming processing tools MS Visual C , OpenCV, OpenCvapplication, MS Kinect SDK"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "No.ore teaching methods Observations Introduction to the intercotion man -based man -based methods 2 Orally and by means multimedia or e- Learning, style of Interactive teaching, Consult. perceptual."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations L - Introduction to OpenCV. The derived framework 2 Orally and by means multimedia or e- Learning, style of Interactive teaching."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Human-calculator interaction evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing the Toretic knowledge and a problem solving skills Written andor oral exam. 50 Laboratory Practical skills to solve and Implementation of problems and of Design specific applications."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Knowledge-Based Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "6.2 Transverse skills CT3 - demonstration of the spirit of initiative and action for Updating professional, economic and culture knowledge organizational 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "Applying the fundamental knowledge of general technical culture and Specialty in solving specific business problems in this field"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "Knowing the fundamental notions of legislation in the field and identification solutions for different problems that may arise within such a business."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations General notions of economic legislation. 2 Modern methods of teaching, Power presentations Point Microsoft Teams The status of the trader."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - 9. Corroboration of the contents of the discipline with the expectations of the community representatives epistemic, professional associations and representative employers in the field related to the program Students will have the opportunity to learn how to put into practice a business idea in the field of specialization studied."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Economic legislation evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course colloquy Written exam 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum performance standard note 5 at the written exam. 33 Date of completion 27.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.Jur."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "2.3 The holder holders of the activities of seminar laboratory project Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "Communication in English in academic and professional context at B1B2 level 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management Projects, with the taking over of the different roles in the team and the clear and concise description, verbal and in writing, in Romanian and in a language of international circulation, a results in the field of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "Development of communicative competence in English, professional context technical and academic."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "After the seminar is completed, the student will be able to - attend meetings, meetings and work activities and formulate opinions, Evaluations and Recommendations in this Frame - Take notes on topics belonging to its specialization field - Read various types of texts in the technical field and extract specific and general information - write and talk about his skills and abilities professional, about his needs and his development in the plan professional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations NA - - - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic reference work of discipline, which exists available to students in a proper number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Formulating questions and answers to questions, within professional meetings."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Limba engleza I evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course NA - - Seminar Student can support tests only if was present at 80 and has solved all Recommended problemsexercises for individual study. Written test evaluation oral of the portfolio Test written 50 Oral evaluation a pORTFOLIO 50 Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final evaluation is solved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Assoc Sonia Munteanu Sonia.munteanulang.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Continuous training"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3. Demonstrating the spirit of initiative and action to update Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing written communication skills in academic context, scientific and technical professional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "The control of information processing strategies and drafting According to discursive models specific to specialized languages - Use of lexical and grammatical structures specific to the scientific domain and technically at the level of advanced competence."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Types of texts in scientificscientific publications. The article 6 lecture conversation Recognition aspects of language, Convention and format in the specialized text Practical exercises of writingunderstanding of specialized text mini projector practical content adapter level the group of study scientific vs the article of popularizing science vs Critical synthesis."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - This is not the case Bibliography Minimal Bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic reference work of discipline that exists available to students in a proper number of copies - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is English language II - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "33 Type activity Evaluation criteria Methods of ASSESSMENT Weight from the final note course The ability to use strategies of information and drafting According to specific discursive models specialized languages. Capacity of elaborating a small text dimensions correctly as format, Linguistic, lexical structures and discursive and page."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "2.3 The holder holders of the activities of seminar laboratory project Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "Minimum level of knowledge of foreign language B1 according to CEFR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "The ability to communicate orally in English in professional context and academic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management Projects, with the taking over of the different roles in the team and the clear and concise description, verbal and in writing, in Romanian and in a language of circulation international, results in the field of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "Developing oral communication skills in English, in context Technical and academic professional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "At the end of the semester the student will be able to - Organize information to support presentations - evaluate the audience and adapt their discourse to the needs of order informational and linguistic - prepare and support a brief lecturepresentation on topics of interest Professional, in the field of specialization, or related to their own interests - to use linguistic and paralinguistic means for various purposes and Communication needs, within an area of interest or the one professional"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference of the discipline, that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Description of the purpose of communication in professional contexts Understanding and differentiating types of presentations Presentations informative, descriptive and argumentative 2 Interactive teaching, work in teampairs, Miniprocts individual and grouppair Group miniprojects or individual Selection exercises and tasks thing is done depending on the level of competence suitable the group, for Each theme 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Limba engleza II evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory The student can support tests only if a formerly present at 80 and a solved all problemsexercises Recommended for individual study. Oral test - Final evaluation written themes Oral test - final 60 The home assessment written 40 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final assessment is resolved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Continuous training"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3 - Demonstration of the spirit of initiative and action for updating Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Knowing the grammatical, format, and conventions regarding Writing technical documents in the foreign language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing the skill to search and use the sources of Information specific to study and draft character documents academic andor scientific - Development of the skill to write in the specialized language. - recognition and understanding of the rhetorical and functional structure of some Professional written genres in the field of engineering sciences."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations The elements of communication. Communication theories classic models, 1 lecture conversation Recognition aspects of language, Convention and format in the specialized text Practical exercises of writingunderstanding of specialized text mini projector practical content organized and adapter level groups of study linguistic and psychosociological."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. 33 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies Will be specified, as the case may be the theme of the seminars, the laboratory works, the theme and the stages of the project."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is English I - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to recognize and understand rhetorical and functional structures of some Professional written genres in the domain engineering sciences. The ability to develop a text of small size correctly As a format, linguistic, lexical structures and discursive and page."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Continuous training"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3 - Demonstration of the spirit of initiative and action for updating Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Knowing the grammatical, format, and conventions regarding Writing technical documents in French"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing the skill to search and use the sources of Information specific to study and drafting documents of academic character andor scientific - Development of the skill to write in the specialized language. - Recognition and understanding of the rhetorical and functional structure of some genres written professional in the field of engineering sciences."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introductory course. Writtenvsspoken in the academicuniversity environment and 1 lecture conversation Recognition aspects of language, convention and formed in the text specialized exercises practical of writingunderstanding of specialized text mini projector practical content I am organized and adapter group level study."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. - - - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is French I - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to recognize and understand rhetorical and functional structures of some Professional written genres in the domain engineering sciences. Capacity to develop a text of small size correctly As a format, linguistic, lexical and discursive and page."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in French language i?",
    "answer": "2.3 Holder Holders of Activities of seminar laboratory project CDA DR. Anamaria lupan, anamarialupanyahoo.com"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French language i?",
    "answer": "Development of communicative competence in French in professional context academic and technical."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French language i?",
    "answer": "After the seminar is completed, the student will be able to - attend meetings, meetings and work activities and formulate opinions, assessments and recommendations in this framework - read various types of texts in the technical field and extract information of specific and general order - write and talk about his professional skills and abilities, about his needs and his professional development - know the specialized lexicon and the characteristics of the language specialized in the language French. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is French language i evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar Student can support tests only if a formerly present at 80 and a solved all recommended exercises for the individual study. Written test Oral rating of portfolio Test written 50 Oral evaluation a pORTFOLIO 50 Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final assessment is solved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Continuous training"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3. Demonstrating the spirit of initiative and action to update professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing written communication skills in academic context, scientific and technical professional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Mastering the strategies for processing information and writing according to discursive models specific to specialized languages - the use of lexical and grammatical structures specific to the knowledgeable domain and technical at the advanced competence level."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introductory course. Types of texts of scientific and technical character."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - 33 The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is French language II - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to use strategies of information and drafting According to specific discursive models specialized languages. The ability to develop a text small in size correctly as format, Linguistic, lexical structures and discursive and page."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in French II?",
    "answer": "2.3 Holder Holders of Activities of seminar laboratory project CDA DR. Anamaria lupan, anamarialupanyahoo.com"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French II?",
    "answer": "Developing oral communication skills in French, in context professional academic and technical."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of French II?",
    "answer": "At the end of the semester the student will be able to - organizes the information in order to support presentations - prepare and support a brief lecturepresentation on topics of interest Professionally, in the field of specialization, or related to their own interests using adequately specialized language - to use linguistic and paralinguistic means for various purposes and Communication needs, within an area of interest or the one professional. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is French II evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar Student can support tests only if a formerly present at 80 and a solved all recommended exercises for the individual study. Oral test - final Evaluation throughoutthemes Oral test - final 60 Evaluation on coursethemes 40 Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final assessment is solved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in German I.?",
    "answer": "6.2 Transverse skills CT2- Identifying the roles and responsibilities in a multi-specialized team, making decisions and assigning tasks, with the application of relationship techniques and effective work within the team."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of German I.?",
    "answer": "Development of communicative competence in technical professional context. 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of German I.?",
    "answer": "the appropriate identification and use of language -specific linguistic means technical - formulating opinions, evaluations and recommendations in writing or oral using the language technical -reading various types of texts Technical denomination and extracting information ordinary and general -The written and oral expression of his professional skills and abilities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in German I.?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. The relevance of the German language in the technical field."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is German I. evaluated?",
    "answer": "33 Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar Student can support tests only if a formerly present at 80 Individual study portfolio is taken in Consider only if taught in time. Written test Oral evaluation of the portfolio of individual study 50 50 Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final evaluation is solved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in German II?",
    "answer": "6.2 Transverse skills CT2 - Identification of roles and responsibilities in a multi -specialized team, making decisions and assigning tasks, with the application of relationship techniques and effective work within the team. 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of German II?",
    "answer": "Development of communicative competence in technical professional context."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of German II?",
    "answer": "After the seminar is completed, the student will be able to - Participate in meetings, meetings and work activities and formulate opinions, evaluations and recommendations in this frame -I notes on topics belonging to its area of specialization -cit various types of texts in the technical field and extract information by specific and general -write and talk about his professional skills and abilities, about his needs and his professional development."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in German II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Restructuring and reformulating information written from texts of specialty."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is German II evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar The student can support tests only if a formerly present at 80 and a solved all problemsexercises Recommended for individual study. Final oral test Evaluation of written themes 60 40 Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The final note is calculated if each component of the final evaluation is solved correctly in proportion of min."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Continuous training"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3 - Demonstration of the spirit of initiative and action for updating Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge 23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Knowing the grammatical, format and conventions regarding Writing technical documents in the foreign language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing the skill to seek and use the sources correctly of information specific to study and drafting character documents academic andor scientific - Development of the skill to write in the specialized language. - recognition and understanding of the rhetorical and functional structure of some Professional written genres in the field of engineering sciences."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations The elements of communication. Communication in the scientific, academic environment and professionally."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. 33 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Foreign Language I German - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to recognize and understand rhetorical and functional structures of some Professional written genres in the domain engineering sciences. The ability to develop a text of small size correctly As a format, linguistic, lexical structures and discursive."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Foreign German language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "CT3. Demonstrating the spirit of initiative and action to update Professional, economic and organizational culture knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Foreign German language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Developing written communication skills in academic context, scientific and technical professional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Foreign German language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "The control of information processing strategies and drafting According to discursive models specific to specialized languages - the appropriate use of lexical and grammatical structures specific to the domain you know and technically"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Foreign German language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Types of popularization of science. The scientific documentary video."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Foreign German language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - 33 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Foreign German language - drafting technical documents evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to use strategies of information and drafting According to specific discursive models specialized languages. The ability to develop a text small in size correctly as format, Linguistic, lexical structures and discursive."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Basic programming knowledge and data structures preferably in C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "C1.3 - building models for different components of computing systems. C1.4 - Formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Knowing the phases, components and algorithms used in Typical language translators Creating a formal base for developing concepts related to lexical and syntactic processors from translators"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Knowing the basic formal models, ie finite automatons and The stack machines, and understanding the relationship in which they are with the definitions of language through regular and grammar expressions Understanding the relationships between the formal description of the automatons in the theory formal languages and their practical implementations as analyzers lexical and syntactic Knowing the classes of languages for which one can implement a Determinist syntactic analyzer Description of the syntax of implemented languages using regular expressions and grammar Designing, developing and testing a software project, using tools specialized software analyzer generators to reach a translator for an artificial language Control of phenomena of ambiguity and indeterminism conflicts which appear in generators of lexical and syntactic analyzers Introduction to methods of processing natural language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Tools for representation rows and rewrite systems, grammar. 2 The main ideas with means multimedia Materials available in the Moodle platform."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Lexical analyzer of C. Regular expressions in Python."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Formal and translator languages evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course - problem solving skills - presence, activity Written test 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory - problem solving skills - presence, activity Laboratory Colloquium 1 and 2 Individual miniproject verification 20 20 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard - Modeling a typical engineering problem using the formal device characteristic of the domain Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature Conf.dr.ing. Anca Mărginean Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This in Management and communication?",
    "answer": "This is not the case"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Management and communication?",
    "answer": "This is not the case"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Management and communication?",
    "answer": "elaboration and implementation of organizational strategies. Knowing the managerial system, as a whole."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Management and communication?",
    "answer": "Identifying roles and responsibilities in a work team and applying of techniques of effective relationship and work within the team. Identifying continuous training opportunities and effective capitalization of resources and learning techniques for their own development."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Management and communication?",
    "answer": "Understanding, assimilating and using concepts, principles, basic techniques of management and communication."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Management and communication?",
    "answer": "understanding and learning managerial functions and roles Example of concrete situations in which the methods are used and the techniques for founding managerial decisions. acquiring the ability to use the most important methods of Management management and techniques."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Management and communication?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to Management Management concept, functions Management, organization managers 2 Interactive course examples and short exercises Discussing topics case studies Short movies on the theme of the course Short projects made by students in teams of 2-3 and discussed at hours The internal environment of the organization 2 The external environment of the organization general and specific 2 The function of planning 2 The function of organization 2 Coordination function 2 The function of performance control and assessment 2 Business communication definition, objectives, functions 2 Types of communication 2 Barriers in communication 2 Conflict and conflict management 2 Assertive communication 2 Written business communication 2 Search for a job CV, interview, letter of Recommendation, etc. 2 33 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Management and communication evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The answer to closed and open questions Involvement in the course of classes I Written exam s 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The condition of obtaining loans n 5 For note 5 the student must know the following the internal and external environment of the organization, the four functions Managerial, Porters five competitive forces, communication process, management -related knowledge conflict in an organization and assertive communication. Date of completion 11.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Sl.dr.ec."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "Skills formed as a result of studying disciplines psychology Education, Pedagogy I, Pedagogy II, Specialty Didactics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "Professional skills C1 Design of training or educational programs adapted for various agetraining levels and various target groups C2 Evaluation of learning processes, results and progress made by students C3 The managerial approach of the group of students, the education process and a learningsocial integration activities specific to the age of the target group C4 Continuous self -assessment and improvement of professional practices and evolution in career C5 Applying the characteristics of student -centered education in design, implementation and Evaluation of the school curriculum Transverse skills CT1 Applying Principles and Norms of Professional Deontology, founded on explicit value options, specific to the specialist in the science of education CT2 Effective cooperation in professional, interdisciplinary, specific work teams conducting projects and programs in the field of education sciences CT3 Use of effective learning methods and techniques throughout life, in the view of continuous training and development"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "Familiarizing students with class management domain of students, with the basic concepts, with the main theories and patterns Applying the Management issue educational at the level of the students class"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "Knowing the meaning of the main concepts within management of the class of students Development of capacities use of concepts Identify the specific of managerial approach in the process of education Analysis of the components of the management class management forming the ability to argue the logical links between Managerial functions and the three processes involved in training School teaching, learning, evaluation forming the ability to argue the logical links between Managerial functions and the three processes involved in training School teaching, learning, evaluation Development of capacities abilities to apply theory Managerial pedagogical in solving some educational situations varied the use of methods of self -assessment of ones own activity of Learning Developing skills to formulate solutions, hypotheses, conclusions For different educational situations offered by theory and practice educational-managerial Identification of educational crisis situations since the phase incipient, their ordering and classification according to specific Determining relevant solutions for different situations of educational crisis compliance with professional deontology rules of the code deontological of the teacher, based on value options explicit, specific to a future teacher Cooperation in working teams to solve different learning tasks improvement of ones own managerial style."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "No. hours Teaching methods Observations Management of the class of students - conceptual delimitations."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "No. hours Teaching methods Observations The teacher - manager of the student class 2 Presentations, debates, case studies, brainstorming, game role, conversation heuristic, the explanation Management of educational relationships and interactions 2 Interpersonal communication 2 Information and learning management 2 Management of disciplinary problems 2 Knowledge of students 2 Management of educational crisis situations in students class 2 Bibliography 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The management of the student class evaluated?",
    "answer": "from the final note"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The management of the student class evaluated?",
    "answer": "The volume and correctness of knowledge Scientific rigor of language The organization of the content originality Ability to highlight applicability theoretical theoretical portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the course 30 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The management of the student class evaluated?",
    "answer": "Design Elaboration and presentation component materialselements of the active participation portfolio at seminars debates, analysis and synthesis some materialscontents, IMPLEMENTATION portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the seminar 20 20 in practice of theoretical content, critical analyzes Originality and creative potential manifested by students within seminar activities and in Preparation of the portfolio."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The management of the student class evaluated?",
    "answer": "50 resulting after summing of the weighted scores according to point 10.3. Date of completion 27.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Project management?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project management?",
    "answer": "Software Development Methodologies, Software Architects"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project management?",
    "answer": "C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project management?",
    "answer": "NA 6. The objectives of the discipline 7.1 The general objective of the discipline The general objective of the discipline is the presentation and analysis of the techniques and software project management tools 7.2 Specific objectives Knowing interfaces and interdependencies between Oose disciplines Presentation and analysis of management techniques and their application in the 2 prominent methodologies Presentation and analysis of monitoring and control techniques metrics and indicators Presentation and analysis of risk management techniques Reflection of software management management techniques 7."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "The use of mathematics, physics, measurement technique, technical graphics, Mechanical, chemical, electric and electronic engineering in computer science and Information technology. Use in professional communication of science concepts, theories and methods Fundamental used in computer science and information technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Solving the usual problems in the field of computer science and technology information by identifying techniques, principles, appropriate methods and by applying Mathematics, with an emphasis on the methods of numerical calculation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "COURSE - Understanding and assimilating concepts, principles and mathematical theories, with Applications in Computer Science and Information Technology - identifying and analyzing specific problems and developing strategies for solving them"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Operation with numbers, functions, series and integals in the complex - Operation with integral and discrete transformations TFI, TFD, Laplace, Z - Using integral and discreet transformations in modeling and Solving some practical, engineering problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations I. Mathematical analysis in the complex - Operations with competition numbers."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Operations with complex numbers Standard, explanation explanation demonstration, examples interaction Monogenous functions. Cauchy-Riemann conditions Holomorphic functions."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Special Mathematics in Engineering evaluated?",
    "answer": "from the final note"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Special Mathematics in Engineering evaluated?",
    "answer": "The acquisition of methods, techniques and theoretical fundamental concepts of the base Written exam course Seminar, i.e. theory problems Written exam 20 theory 80 problem"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Special Mathematics in Engineering evaluated?",
    "answer": "The degree of development of practical skills and operating capacity with notions, the fundamental techniques and methods introduced Written exam course Seminar, i.e. theory problems Final note 80 written exam 20 actvity seminar and Materials ADDITIONAL"
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Special Mathematics in Engineering evaluated?",
    "answer": "Note on written examination to be at least 5 Date of completion 24.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of this discipline?",
    "answer": "Presentation of the concepts, notions and fundamental methods used in enumerative combination and in the theory of discrete probabilities. Presentation of the basic notions and properties with which the theory operates graphs Mathematical models using concepts and methods from graph theory algorithms and basic theorems of graph theory and demonstration."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of this discipline?",
    "answer": "Elaborating strategies to solve and apply the methods of Specific reasoning in solving combinatorial problems. Identification of combinatorial patterns patterns to solve the problems of counting."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is this discipline evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to understand and use the concepts discipline in mathematical reasoning applied to concrete problems. Written exam 50 Seminar Problem solving skills."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Mathematical Analysis I Differential calculus?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Mathematical Analysis I Differential calculus?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Mathematical analysis II Integral calculus and differential equations?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Ing. Cornel Moisescu - cornel.moisescucs.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "C5 - Design, maintenance and operation of modern processing systems, Data storage and transmissions C5.1 - Identification and description of solutions design instruments of processing, storage and data transmission C5.2 - Using interdisciplinary knowledge for insurance exploitation of computer systems C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security and confidentiality of computer systems C5.4 - Qualitative testing and evaluation of functional characteristics and non -functional computer systems, based on specific criteria C5.5 - Design of computer systems starting from maximizing pERFORMANCE"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Maintenance of computer systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Design, Design, Implementation, Operation and Maintenance Systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Trends in the IT industry 4 Basic concepts for data processing 2 Data processing servers, vm, cloud, hybrid 2 Update new trends in the IT industry 2 Data storage 2 Technologies in the field of data storage 2 Data transmission networks 2 Backup 2 Management of computer systems 2 Convergent architectures 2 Hybrid architectures 2 Security of computer systems 2 Design and Design of Information Systems Infrastructure 2 Analysis and detailing project exam 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "General standards for computer architectures 1 Design Infrastructure Information System 1 Test 1 - Design Infrastructure Information System 1 Design Infrastructure Information System for Data Management 1 Security Design Infrastructure Information System 1 Design Data Data Data Design 1 Test 2 - Design of HIBID DATA HIBID SOLUTIONS 1 Design performance levels in storage solutions 1 Application of secure and confidentialization concepts data in solutions storage 1 Test 3 - Design Solutions Date Lake 1 Preparation of the exam project 1 Preparation of the exam project 1 Preparation of the exam project 1 33 Preparation of the exam project 1 The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Maintenance of computer systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Basic knowledge of architects Oral examination 50 computer systems technologies, Datacenter, servers, storage, administration Seminar - - - Laboratory Is able to design systems computer science for implementing some Applications test 50 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Understand the basic principles of a computer system and can issue and argue the choice of solutions for implementation of applications. Calculation Discipline note 50 laboratory 50 final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 27.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "COMETENTS IN ELEMENTARY DIFFERENTIAL Equations, integral calculation, series."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "C1 The use of mathematics, engineering and computer science. C1.1 The use in the professional communication of concepts, theories and the methods of the fundamental sciences used in systems engineering."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "Numerical methods for solving linear equations and equations systems nonlinear, interpolation methods, quadrature formulas, numerical methods for differential equations elements of approximation theory."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "Numerical methods for resolving linear equations systems Methods direct and iterative methods Numerical methods of solving non -linear equations bisective method, method to Newton, the method of the sequence, the quasi-thewton methods Interpolation methods polynomial interpolation and spleen interpolation Formulas of quadrature degree of accuracy, Gauss quadrature formulas Methods numerical for differential equations Explicit Eulers Method, Method of Default euler, run-kutta methods Elements of approximation Bernstein polynomials, bezier curves, operators of approximation. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Numerical methods evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course The acquisition of theoretical knowledge and to problem solving skills with specific character. Written exam 30 Applications The ability to solve problems and application of algorithms Written exam 70 Laboratory Active participation in all hours of laboratory."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Methodology of drafting projects?",
    "answer": "C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - The proper use of quality, safety and security standards in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including the identification and analysis of the problem, Designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Methodology of drafting projects?",
    "answer": "1. Be able to write a project proposal 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Methodology of drafting projects?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction - types of projects 2 Onsite Selecting the project 2 Preparation of project proposal 2 Research and research process 2 Research methods 2 Search and Review of Specialized Literature 2 The report 2 Structure of the report 2 Writing the report 2 The management of cities and references 2 Referent styles 2 Presentation and discussion of remarkable projects 2 Oral presentation 2 Discussion and defense 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Dawson, C.W."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Methodology of drafting projects?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - 33 The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Methodology of drafting projects evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Oral oral colloquium 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 100 Final exam Condition of participation in the final exam present at min 50 of the course activity. Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 23.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Methodology of project preparation?",
    "answer": "C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - The proper use of quality, safety and security standards in taking over information C5.5 - carrying out a project including the identification and analysis of the problem, Designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Methodology of project preparation?",
    "answer": "Be able to write a project proposal Be able to carry out the search for bibliography and to evaluate critically other written works Be able to use cities and references in written technical reports Be able to write the final report of the project Be able to be able to discuss quality about the project"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Methodology of project preparation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction - types of projects 2 Onsite Selecting the project 2 Preparation of project proposal 2 Research and research process 2 Research methods 2 Search and Review of Specialized Literature 2 The report 2 Structure of the report 2 Writing the report 2 The management of cities and references 2 Referent styles 2 Presentation and discussion of remarkable projects 2 Oral presentation 2 Discussion and defense 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Dawson, C.W."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Methodology of project preparation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - 33 The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Methodology of project preparation evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Oral oral colloquium 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Disciplinary note 100 Final examination Participation condition in examination Final present at min 50 of the course activity. Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 23.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "Mathematics, physics, electrical and electronic engineering"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with scientific, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware, software and communications systems C1.3 - building models for different components of systems calculation C1.4 - Formal evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of computing systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems C2 - Designing hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of functional and non -functional features of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "1. Identification of the objectives to achieve, the available resources, the conditions of completed them, work stages, working times, terms of accomplishment and related risks."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "The purpose of the course is to make the first student contact of the student with Technique of electrical and electronic measurements, knowledge of domain non -electric measurements, main sizes and methods to measure, as well as Sensor integration into modern technological systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "After completing the discipline the students will be able To know how to identify the measuring devices and read the indication of a device measure To know how to use measuring appliances according to measured size To know how to read a measurement scheme To know how to interpret the result of a measure and the related error be able to estimate the quality and accuracy of the measurement process to choose sensors for a particular practical situation to implement a system of measuring a non -electric sizes to assess the accuracy of the measurements to optimize measurement systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Electronic measures."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. The use of analog measuring devices, 2 The teaching process uses presentations multimedia Power point, Onsite interaction, with Students on ISSUES addressed, materials distributed to students, hours of consultations, studies in case."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Electronic measurements and sensors evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Written exam 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory Activity and presence in hours laboratory. Evaluation of reports from Laboratory works 0 Design - - - Minimum performance standard The laboratory ending is mandatory for entering the exam."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Numerical Methods?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Numerical Methods?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Object Oriented Programming?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "Conf. Univ."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "competences formed as a result of studying discipline Education psychology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "C1 Design of training or educational programs adapted for various agetraining levels and various target groups C2 Realization of activities specific to the instructional-educational process in Gymnasium education C6 Continuous self -assessment and improvement of professional practices and a career evolution C7 Use of scientific research and data processing methods in the field of education 26 C8 Applying the characteristics of student -centered education in design, implementation and evaluation of the school curriculum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "CT1 Applying the principles and norms of professional deontology, based on explicit value options, specific to the specialist in science education CT2 Efficient cooperation in professional, interdisciplinary work teams, Specific to carrying out projects and programs in the field of science education CT3 Use of efficient learning methods and techniques throughout life, for the training and continuous professional development CT4 Promoting the values associated with making quality education, in compliance with internal educational policies and in accordance with the elaborated ones and popularized at European level, based on knowing the specificity of the domain European educational and interculturality."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "Formation of skills aiming at knowledge, interpretation, processing and Applying the issue specific to contemporary education and pedagogy and the theory and methodology of the curriculum within the didactic steps of conduct of instructional-educational activities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "the correct identification of the empirical references of the pedagogical concepts and conceptual meanings of educational phenomena Knowing the meaning of the main concepts within the theory curriculum Developing the capacities of using concepts for critical analysis of curricular processes and products analyzing the trends of developing contemporary pedagogy, in the context of the education and education reform in our country analyzing the tendencies of education in the society of knowledge of the 21st century outlining a global and relevant image on the issue of education and contemporary pedagogy The proposal of some ways of articulating and integrating the types and forms of education Analysis of the concept of permanent education and institutional system based on this principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Remark Desiders and Perspectives of Education and Education in the century XXI. Educational policies and practices in the context of system reform of Romanian education Priorities of educational policies in Romania directions of the reform The education system in Romania Desiders and Perspectives of Basic Education in policies European and world educational The role of mandatory education in all the national system of education 2 lecture heuristic conversation DISCUSSION Problem the debate with imaginary opponent the exercise of reflection case studies, brainstorming the explanation video supports Pedagogy - Education Science The establishment of pedagogy as a science The scientific character of the pedagogy The system of education sciences The interdisciplinary character of pedagogy as science Traditional pedagogy - contemporary pedagogy 2 Education - object of study of pedagogy Education - concept, meanings The functions of education The characteristics of education 2 36 The structure of the educational action New dimensions and tendencies of education in the 21st century Diversification of the field of education Forms of education formal education, non -formal education, education informal Permanent education Self -education - quality of modern man 2 Components and ways of education Components of complex and harmonious education of personality intellectual, moral, aesthetic, religious, technological, physical New fields and ways of education intercultural, inclusive, ecological, nutritional etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Directions of the reform of the education system in Romania the role mandatory education in the whole of national system of education 2 Presentations, debates, case studies, brainstorming, role play, the heuristic conversation, the explanation Traditional pedagogy - contemporary pedagogy 2 The characteristics of education The structure of the educational action 2 Forms of education formal education, non -formal education, education informal Permanent education Self -education - quality of modern man 2 Components of complex and harmonious education of personality intellectual, moral, aesthetic, religious, technological, physical 2 Factors of psychic development heredity, environment, education The interaction of factors and the leading role of education 2 Operationalization of educational objectives - applications, examples 2 Traditional and modern in approaching the contents of education levels of curricular integration intradisciplinarity monodisciplinarity multidisciplinarity 2 56 pluridiciplinarity interdisciplinarity transdisciplinarity. Curricular structures and typologies Curriculum nucleus and curriculum at School decision, formalnon -formalinformal curriculum, taughtlearned, university curriculum Elaboration of an optional program CDS 4 Curricular Products Analysis Education Plan Program School discipline sheets, school textbooks, other supports Curricular guides, educational, methodical, auxiliary software didactics."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Pedagogy I the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The volume and correctness of the knowledge Scientific language organization of content Originality The ability to highlight the applicability of the theme notional portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the course 30 30 Seminarlaboratory Design Elaboration and presentation of materials the component elements of the portfolio Active participation in seminars debates, analysis and synthesis of some materialscontent, the transposition into practice of contents theoretical, critical analyzes Originality and creative potential manifested by students in seminar activities and in the preparation of the portfolio. portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the seminar 20 20 Minimum Performance Standard 50 resulting after summing of the weighted scores according to point 10.3."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "Conf. Univ."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "competences formed as a result of studying discipline Education psychology, Pedagogy I."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "C1 Design of training or educational programs adapted for various agetraining levels and various target groups C2 Realization of activities specific to the instructional-educational process in Gymnasium education C6 Continuous self -assessment and improvement of professional practices and a 26 career evolution C7 Use of scientific research and data processing methods in the field of education C8 Applying the characteristics of student -centered education in design, implementation and evaluation of the school curriculum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "CT1 Applying the principles and norms of professional deontology, based on explicit value options, specific to the specialist in science education CT2 Efficient cooperation in professional, interdisciplinary work teams, Specific to carrying out projects and programs in the field of science education CT3 Use of efficient learning methods and techniques throughout life, for the training and continuous professional development CT4 Promoting the values associated with making quality education, in compliance with internal educational policies and in accordance with the elaborated ones and popularized at European level, based on knowing the specificity of the domain European educational and interculturality."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "acquiring skills aiming at knowledge, interpretation, processing and applying the problem of training theory and methodology and a theory and methodology of evaluation, the ways of organizing the activity school on the principle of efficient quality and capitalization of resources"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "Knowing the meaning of the main concepts within the theory and methodology of training and evaluation theory and methodology Development the capacities of use of concepts the correct identification of the empirical references of the pedagogical concepts and the conceptual meanings of the teaching-learning-evaluation processes The correct and in various contexts of the terminology specific to the theory and methodology of training and theory and methodology of evaluation analyzing the ways of approaching the education process identifying some ways of articulating and integrating methods and training strategies in the education process Identify new opportunities for approaching methods and procedures educational from the perspective of elaborating training strategies Operation with the concepts, structures and typologies involved in the activity of school evaluation Proposing correct, objective and objective evaluation methods and procedures significant of the students school performance Elaboration of educational projects, based on teaching strategies coherent, which facilitates individual learning styles and modes of organization of the education process Elaboration of design models by applying normativity in didactic activities developing positive motivation and favorable attitude towards The didactic profession, receptivity and responsibility for changes innovative in the field of general didactics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Remark Didactics - general theory of the education process Current Educational Paradigms and Orientations Didactics - definition, features, functions The object of study of didactics The sub -branches of the didactics Directions of development of contemporary didactics 2 lecture heuristic conversation DISCUSSION Problem The process of education - systemic approach 2 36 Definition of concepts education system, education process Defining notes of the education process The systemic approach to the education process the debate with imaginary opponent the exercise of reflection case studies, brainstorming the explanation video supports The process of education - communication approach Communication - concept, structure Forms of communication Didactic communication Definition and characteristics of didactic communication Structural elements of didactic communication Sources of distortion in didactic communication Efficiency of didactic communication 2 The interactional approach to the education process Teaching - the essential component of the education process The concept of teaching traditional and modern meanings forms of teaching teaching styles Learning concepts of learning and school learning learning styles 2 The system of didactic principles Teaching principles concept, features The system of didactic principles The principle of the theory of theory with the practice The principle of accessibility of complying with age features and individual The principle of intuition of the correlation between concrete and abstract, between sensory and rational The principle of systematization and continuity in learning The principle of conscious and active participation of students The principle of thorough learning 2 Didactic methodology Conceptual delimitations didactic technology, didactic methodology, teaching strategy, education method, didactic process Current tendencies on didactic methodology Education methods Methods of communicating and acquiring socio -cultural values Methods of systematic exploration of objective reality Methods based on practical action Methods of rationalizing the contents and operations of teaching learning 6 The means of education The concept of means of education The functions of the means of education The taxonomy of the means of education Requirements for selecting and using the means of education. 2 Lesson - basic form of organizing the education process The variety of forms of organization of the education process Concept, evolution, classification Lesson - fundamental form of organizing the process of education Definition of lesson Valences and lesson critics Variables and pedagogical requirements of lesson Fundamental types of lessons 2 Evaluation in the education process Definition and analysis of concepts evaluation, measurement, appreciation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Traditional teaching modern didactics. Student focus - objective of modern didactics."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Pedagogy II training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The volume and correctness of knowledge Scientific rigor of language The organization of the content originality The ability to highlight the applicability of the theme notional portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the course 30 30 Seminarlaboratory Design Elaboration and presentation of materials the component elements of the portfolio Active participation in seminars debates, analysis and synthesis of some materialscontent, the transposition into practice of contents theoretical, critical analyzes Originality and creative potential manifested by students in seminar activities and in the preparation of the portfolio. portfolio Current observation a active participation a students at the seminar 20 20 Minimum Performance Standard 50 resulting after summing of the weighted scores according to point 10.3."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - The use of interdisciplinary knowledge, the print patterns and a tools, conducting experiments and interpreting their results C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - The appropriate use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "CT1 - Honorable, Responsible, Ethics behavior, in the spirit of the law to ensures the reputation of the profession CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management projects, taking over different team roles and clear description and concise, verbal and writing, in Romanian and in a language of circulation international, results in the field of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Applying fundamental and applicative knowledge acquired in development a project within a specialized or research collective company theme established by the project leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Familiarizing students with methodologies and technologies specific to activities of design and implementation and involvement of students in making some Simple hardwaresophwareeducational communications projects - Participation in courses and training activities organized by the company or The ECRCEARS group to which the practice is performed - analysis and documentation - study and familiarization with specific design and implementation tools - Designing, implementing, testing and validating some projects modules simple with educational role"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. Bibliography -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations study and documentation study of used methodologies and or technologies Implementation of testing and validating some components simple modules with educational purpose Documentation of implemented components Bibliography For the elaboration of the project, the bibliography is the one recommended by the project manager from the company or the collective of correction to which the implementation as well as the result of the documentation is realized. 33 The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Practica de domeniu evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course NA NA NA Practice Presence min. 100 h, activity, appreciation tutor from the companyfaculty Oral colloquium."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and methods ENGINEERING C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives of resolution, to optimize performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.5 - carrying out a project including the identification and analysis of the problem, Designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "CT1 - Honorable, Responsible, Ethics behavior, in the spirit of the law to ensures the reputation of the profession CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management projects, taking over different team roles and clear description and concise, verbal and writing, in Romanian and in a language of circulation international, results in the field of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Applying fundamental and applicative knowledge acquired in development a project within a specialized or research collective company theme established by the project leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Familiarizing and involving students in each stage of making a HardwareSofwareCommunications Project Complex as well as with the aspects CONNEXEXI DESIGN ACTIVITY - Designing, implementing, testing and validating the project - Elaboration of documentation, technical reports - Taming and developing communication skills - project management activities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations This is not the case. Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations analysis of the product made Developing a project specification implementing and installing the hardware or software system testing and validating the product product documentation Bibliography For the elaboration of the project, the bibliography is the one recommended by the project manager from the company or the collective of correction to which the implementation as well as the result of the documentation is realized. The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Specialized practice evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course NA NA NA Practice Presence min. 100 h, activity, appreciation tutor from the companyfaculty Oral colloquium 100 Minimum performance standard making a softwarehardwarecommunications engineering project."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Computer operating skills Word, Excel, Power Point and Internet Explorer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "C1. Use, interpretation, processing and application of knowledge Psycho -pedagogical and methodological specialty in the frame of the entire didcatical approach Design of instructional-educational activities and teaching materials C2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "CT1 - applying the principles and norms of professional deontology Fundamental on explicit value options, specific to the specialist in science education. CT2 - Effective cooperation in professional, interdisciplinary work teams, specific to the densification of educational projects and programs CT3 - Use of efficient learning methods and techniques throughout life for vocational training and development CT4 - promoting the values of quality education, according to internal educational policies and in accordance with those elaborated and popularized at European level."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Knowing the specificity of the research of the education process characteristics, stages, functions, types, methodologies, etc. from the pebigogical practices."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Developing the ability to observe, record, analyze and appreciate instructional-educational activities Formation of a system of operating capacities to design, achieve and Evaluate instructional-educational activities the ability to design activities Inegral, of different types and variants, as well as other forms of organization of the education process the ability to completely conduct activities of different typesvariants the ability to measure, appreciate, decide on carrying out activities, the ability to adjustautoregla activities in depending on the results of the evaluation Developing the ability to collaborate with different educational factors, training them in instructional-educational activities."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Observation and full recording of different typesvariants of lessons, with the help of school instruments grids, sheets, guides, etc.."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Practica pedagogica nivel I licenta evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Practice Observative practice Effective practice. Practice portfolio EDUCATION 100 Minimum Performance Standard teaching the portfolio with annual teaching projects, learning units and lesson project teaching a set of evaluation samples."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "Computer operating skills Word, Excel, Power Point and Internet Explorer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "C1. The use, interpretation, processing and application of specialized knowledge psycho -pedagogical and methodological in the frame of the entire didcatic design approach of instructional-educational activities and teaching materials C2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "CT1 - Applying Principles and Nhormles of Professional Deontology Fundamental on explicit value options, specific to the specialist in science education. CT2 - Effective cooperation in professional, interdisciplinary work teams, specific to carrying out educational projects and programs CT3 - Use of efficient learning methods and techniques throughout life for vocational training and development CT4 - Promoting the values of a quality education, in compliance with the internal educational policies and in accordance with those elaborated and popularized at European level."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "COURSE Knowing the specificity of the research of the education process characteristics, stages, functions, types, methodologies, etc. from the perspective the pedagogical practice carried out in pre -university education."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "Developing the ability to observe, record, analyze and appreciate instructional-educational activities Formation of a system of operating capacities to design, achieve and Evaluate instructional-educational activities the ability to design activities Integral, of different types and variants, as well as other forms of organization of the education process the ability to completely conduct activities of different typesvariants the ability to measure, appreciate, decide on When carrying out activities, the ability to adjustself -regulating activities depending on the results of the evaluation Developing the ability to collaborate with different educational factors, training them in instructional-educational activities."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - - - - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Observation and integration of the integral of different Typesvariants of lessons, with the help of instruments school grids, files, guides, etc.. 4 Analysis, debate and appreciation of the lessons in the group observed, at least 3-4 variants of lessons for Each type of lesson category and 1-2 forms of activity."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Pedagogical practice II evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Practice Observative practice Effective practice. Practice portfolio EDUCATION 100 Minimum Performance Standard 70 resulting after weighted punctures Date of completion 10.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course - Applications Assist.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Diploma project leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "C4 - contextual integration and exploitation of dedicated computer systems C4.1 - Establishing relevant criteria regarding quality and security in computer systems C4.2 - Using multidisciplinary knowledge for integration computer systems C4.3 - Using new concepts and methods for insurance Security, safety and ease of exploitation of systems integrated computer science C4.4 - Elaboration of tests, use and adaptation of standards of Quality, safety and security in dedicated computer systems C4.5 - carrying out interdisciplinary research and development projects with Respecting the stages of quality, security and safety C5 - Research, development and optimization of computer systems combining Multidisciplinary knowledge C5.1 - Demonstration of the knowledge of the principles of the functionalities of the systems COMPUTER C5.2 - Use of the ability to interpret new situations from different fields of science C5.3 - Creative combination of different principles of research and development modern from interdisciplinary fields, with computer components C5.4 - Use of quality assessment criteria and methods for Optimization of computer systems in various fields C5.5 - Completion of practical research activities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Elaboration of the diploma work"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "To achieve these general goals, students will integrate the results obtained in the research activity in a work in accordance with the requirements DEPARTMENT"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography For the elaboration of the diploma work, the bibliography is the one recommended by the project manager and the one resulting from the documentation. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Practice for the diploma project evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design Diploma work Diploma work 100 Minimum Performance Standard Diploma work 33 Date of completion 11.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course - Applications The Diploma Work leader Date of approval in the Council of Computer Department 20.02.2024 Director of Department, Prof.dr.ing. Rodica Potolea Date of approval in the Faculty of Automation and Computers Council 22.02.2024 Dean, Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Practical work in the domain of study?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Development of applications in C language, architecture of graphic systems, sequence graphic processing pipelines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Study and experimentation of 3D photorealist graphic algorithms. Development 2D and 3D graphics applications."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Building the graphic model of a 3D object scene Implementation and use of basic 3D graphic algorithms in the nucleus of a graphic system Construction of graphic applications in a high-level language C, C using graphic libraries eg. Openngl Implementing the main phases of the transformation sequence graphics, for transforming a scene of 3D objects into picture"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Computational graphics. Mathematics items used in graphics 2 Means are used multimedia of teaching at the course."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Administrative organization 2 The structure of an OpenGL application 2 Primitive graphic in OpenGL 2 34 Graphic transformations in OpenGL 2 Documentation and The examples are available on the course server."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Graphic processing evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The written exam tests the understanding and the ability to apply knowledge acquired at the course. The activity at the course evaluates the participation Active students in discussions and analyzes from the course throughout the semester."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Image processing?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Image processing?",
    "answer": "Programming in C language, linear algebra and analytical geometry, mathematics Special, Numerical Calculation, Physics Optics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Image processing?",
    "answer": "C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - the use of domain specific tools for explanation and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Image processing?",
    "answer": "Understanding the concepts related to images, artificial vision and processing images. Acquire and use of image processing methods and Design of specific applications."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Image processing?",
    "answer": "Knowledge, evaluation and use of concepts, algorithms and specific methods Image processing formats of representation of digital images, The camera model, statistical analysis, filtration, quality restoration improvement, segmentation, measurements. Developing the ability to find optimal implementation solutions from the point of time and resources Developing the capabilities of qualitative and quantitative evaluation of the results, a algorithms and systems based on image processing Knowing and using specific programming processing tools Visual C , OpenCV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Image processing?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introductory notions 2 Orally and by means multimedia or e- Learning, style of Interactive teaching, Consult, involvement students in activities of Design. NA Chamber model intrinsic and extrinsic parameters."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Image processing?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Obs. L- Introduction to the use of OpenCV library 2 Presentation on the board and by means multimedia or Elearning Experiments and implementation using tools specific ms visual Studio, OpenCV Evaluation of stages of design and implementation NA L- color spaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Image processing evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing Toretic knowledge and skills of problem solving Written exam. 50 Laboratory Practical skills to solve and Implementation of problems and design Specific applications."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "No previous functional programming knowledge is required, but it is Recommended to have a minimum experience of one year of programming in a Language like Java, C or C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "C2 - Designing a software system in the functional manner C2.1 - Identification and description of system software components C2.2 - Explanation of the role each component and their interaction. C2.3 - Construction of software components using methods of Design, languages, technologies and tools specific to programming Functional."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Developing the correct, concise code writing on the basis of the paradigm elements functional immutability of variables, high level of abstraction, possibility formal demonstration of the correctness of a program, the possibility of easy parallelization of the code as well as its foundations Theoretical Lambda Calculation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Functional programming?",
    "answer": "To achieve these general objectives, students will learn - to write code in the functional manner, with the elimination of the state variables - To identify the advantages and disadvantages of different programming styles - to use recussion and structure the code for its optimization - to use higher order functions - to exploit the mechanisms of lazy evaluation and infinite structures - to formally demonstrate the correctness of a program - to handle the basic lambda expressions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Programming paradigms."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to functional programming using ELM 2 Exercise resolution and problems, implementation of computer functions, drawing of algorithms Tipurin in Elm 2 Lists and recursion 2 Higher -order functions in ELM 2 Evaluation ELM 2 MINIAPLICATION ELM 2 Introduction to Haskell. Lists, recursion 2 Checking of types in Haskell 2 Trees in Haskell 2 Haskell 2 Lazy evaluation and infinite lists 2 Miniaplication in Haskell 2 Calculation lambda 2 Haskell evaluation 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Functional programming evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Understanding the specific concepts of paradigm of functional programming and its base theoretical. Active participation in the course, themes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Logical programming?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems 24 C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Logical programming?",
    "answer": "The major objective of the discipline is the accumulation of processing knowledge Symboliclogic, and competences in description of specifications in logical format, directly executable. Also the evaluation of the performance of the logical applications developed."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Logical programming?",
    "answer": "Declarative and procedural semantics Extra-logic operators Meta-programming Data structures in logical programming, techniques related to estimate effectiveness Incomplete structure, difference lists Types of recursion with advantages and limitations Developing complex applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Logical programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction, procedural semantics and declarative semantics in 2 Interactive course. Teaching board with Examples, questions and Discussions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Logical programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Prologue language 2 Seminar works individual laboratory, with the specific theme. Seminar- solutions of problems at tabla."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Logical programming evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solutions using techniques specific Final exam Fe writtenoral 50 2-3 Evaluations to the course Quiz, on the course of the semester writtenmoodle 20 Seminar Problem solving Practical test LAB computer 30 Laboratory Design NA NA NA Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 20 quiz writtenmoodle during course min 2 max 3 assessments, equal weights average 30 Laboratory Evaluation of each topic, equal weights average 50 Final exam Fe The laboratory examination is held at most 2 times a year 1 in the normal session and 1 in the session of arrears. Conditions of participation in the final exam Laboratory colloquium 5 Conditions of promotion Final examination 5 Disciplinary note5 FE evaluation quiz moodle, for Fe 7 Oral examination, problem solving, PT 7 Fe 10 optional, registration conditions eliminators, depending on other notes Overdue Quiz Moodle Maximum note 5 Increased note and note in arrears 5 oral examination provided it is obtained the passing note to the Moodle exam Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "Using a procedural programming language such as C language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, Data structures, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "Rigorous learning of object -oriented programming concepts using Java programming language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "to design objects oriented on smallmedium -scale problems demonstrate the differences between traditional imperative design and Object -oriented design explain the class structures as fundamental building blocks, modulation understand the role of inheritance, polymorphism, dynamic bonding and generic structures in the construction of the reusable code write Java programs on a smallmedium scale with simple graphic interface use classes written by other programmers when they build systems be able to design and build simple graphic interfaces Gui."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Concepts and paradigms in object -oriented programming. The environment Java."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Use of Java development averages 2 Primitive types and simple entryoutput in Java 2 Variables and expressions in Java 2 Flow control and simple classes in Java 2 Classes, objects and paintings 2 Inheritance in Java 2 Laboratory test 1 2 Interfaces in Java 2 Treating exceptions in Java 2 Collections and generic types 2 Testing of object oriented programs 2 Graphic interfaces. Treating events 2 Graphic interfaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Object -oriented programming evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Poo concepts Problem solving skills using Poo paradigm Course tests T final exam Written s 60 50 e 10 t Seminar - - - Laboratory The quality of laboratory applications and Evaluation of laboratory tests Analysis and evaluation of solutions issues 40 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam and tests Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 44 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing. Raluca Brehar Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Programare Web?",
    "answer": "OOP programming skills Working skills with databases Skills of a Design applications using multi-level architectures."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Programare Web?",
    "answer": "C4 - Design and integration of computer systems using technologies and medium programming C4.1 - Identification and description of technologies and environments of programming and of the specific concepts of programming engineering 23 C4.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components computer systems C4.3 - Elaboration of specifications and designing some computer systems using specific methods and tools C4.4 - Management of life cycle of hardware, software and of communications based on performance assessment C4.5 - Development, implementation and integration of computer systems C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Programare Web?",
    "answer": "Design, development, integration and exploitation of web computer systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Programare Web?",
    "answer": "Designing, developing, integrating and operating a computer system Web on the client side. Designing, developing, integrating and operating a computer system Web on the server side."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Programare Web?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Theme1 - designing and developing a web application using 12 Presentation theme of 33 HTMLXHTML, Javascript and CSS laboratoryworks of Seminar, discussions and questions, verification progress, evaluation Theme2 - Designing and developing a web application using AJAX and php 10 Theme3 - Design and develop a web application using Python 10 Theme4 - Development and integration of web services 10 Bibliography 1. Fundamentals of Web Development, 2nd Edition."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Programare Web evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to conceptualize, synthesize and Analyze the specific problems in the field the design and development of systems Web computer. Written exam 50 Seminar The ability to use different techniques and Technologies in designing and developing Web computer systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Writing programs in a programming language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and communications components Using design methods, languages, algorithms, data structures, protocols"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Studying and learning programming techniques in assembly language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Studying the basic concepts of an assembly language - Studying the defining elements of ISA X86 architecture - Acquiring the Assembly Language of the Intel X86 processor family - Learning programming techniques specific to a low level language - Writing programs in assembly language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction, information representation. Multimedia means - Power presentations Point Storage and access to data, ISA X86 architecture - types of units of Storage, the basic elements of ISAX86 architecture registers, indicators, address modes, memory addresses calculation Format of Instructions X86, Execution of Instructions - Syntax and The Format of IsaX86 instructions, the phases and modes of execution of to an instruction The Directives of the Assembly Language MASM X86 - Directives for Declating variables, constants, segments and a procedures, program prototype written in assembly language ISA X86 Instruction Set - Transfer instructions, instructions arithmetic and logical The Set of Instructions ISA X86 continued - jump instructions, routine calls, rotation and travel operations The Set of Instructions ISA X86 continued - operations on strings, Interruption instructions, conditions on condition indicators, Instructions 386 instructions to the co -acquisor mathematical - architecture to the mathematical coprocessor, transfer instructions, instructions of conversion Instructions of the Mathematical Coprocessor continued Instructions arithmetic in the floating comma MMX technology architecture and instructions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Representation of information 35 ISA X86 architecture, addressing modes, troubleshooting utility Presentation to the board, writing and troubleshooting programs on computer. Modes of addressing and calculating memory addresses Use of directives ISA X86 Instruction Set transfer operations, arithmetic and logical The Set of Instructions ISA X86 rows operations, routine call The Set of Instructions ISA X86 jump instructions, other instructions Floating comma operations The programming of complex applications Operations on SIR type data and matrix Optimizing the programs written in assembly language Access techniques to a computers resources Advanced programming techniques in assembly language colloquy Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Programming in assembly language evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - degree of knowledge of basic concepts - programming skills in language of assembly Written exam. 70 Seminar - - - Laboratory - Skills to write specific functions In the assembly language - Skills to solve a problem complexes made within the laboratory Written colloquium and evaluation activities carried on the course of the semester."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer programming?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with mathematical, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware, software and communications systems C1.3 - building models for different components of systems calculation C1.4 - Formal evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of computing systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer programming?",
    "answer": "Learning the use of a high -level language for writing programs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer programming?",
    "answer": "Understanding the small -sized issues exposed in natural language and Development of solutions in the form of computer programs Understanding the source code written by other programmers and the ability to analyze Critical that code Designing and implementing programs in C language using a structured modular approach Learning a proper programming style Identification of the causes of programming errors and correcting them."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computer programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Programming languages. The stages of solving problems using the computer."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Computer programming?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations S1.The representation of algorithms logical and pseudocode schemes 1 Guidance, discussions, problem solutions. Guidance, discussions and the assisted development of programs."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Computer programming evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Programming concepts in C language Problem solving skills using C programming language Course tests T final exam Written s 60 50 e 10 t Seminar Problem solving using the language of programming C. Verification of themes - Laboratory The quality of laboratory apps and evaluation laboratory test Evaluation of problem solving at test 40 Design - - - 44 Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam and tests Conditions for participation in the final exam Laboratory 5, seminar realized topics Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 Date of completion 31.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Discipline Computer Networks Discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "C5 - Designing, managing life cycle, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods to ensure security, safety and ease in operation of computing systems C5.4 - the appropriate use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "CT2 - Identification, description and conduct of processes in the management projects, taking over different team roles and clear description and concise, verbal and writing, in Romanian and in a language of circulation international, results in the field of activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Designing a medium complexity network in a team of 3 to 4 students"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Calculation of quantities, selecting equipment, equipment configuration, allocation IP addresses, use of network simulator"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction, organization of project teams, specifying requirements 4 Project Realization Stage 1 4 Making Project Stage 2 4 Project Realization Stage 3 4 Elaboration of Documentation of Project 1 4 Elaboration of Documentation of Project 2 4 Supporting the project, colloquium 4 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Packet Tracer Usage Manual, Opnet, 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Project Protocols and Communications networks evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - 33 Design Compliance with the project requirements Check if the project is according to the specifications. Projects submitted online by e- mail 100 Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Note Discipline 100 Final note Participation conditions in the final exam Maximum an absence at project hours, intermediate projects of the project taught at the set deadlines."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Hardware design, programming in assembly language, language programming C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components 2 credits C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and C5 communication - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity of hardware, software and communications 3 credits C5.2 - Using multidisciplinary knowledge for adaptation to the calculation systems at specific problems of the application domain C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Knowing, understanding and using the concepts of microprocessor microcontroller, bus, memory system, data transfer methods, interface circuits and interface of peripheral devices, analysis and Designing systems with microprocessors."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "To achieve the main goal, the specific objectives are pursued Knowing the capabilities of microprocessors and microcontrollers Used hardware capabilities, instruction set architecture, Assembly language, programming solutions. kNOWLEDGE components hardware use together with Microprocessor electrical, logical characteristics, connection modes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to microprocessor systems. The family of 2 Orally and by means multimedia, style Interactive teaching, Consultations, involvement students in Research activities Design."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Laboratory Presentation on the board, plate experiments development with microcontroller Arduino, ESP32, peripheral modules, sensors, Ide- use Specialized URI for design Arduino Ide, Atmel Studio, involvement students in Research projects. NA Introduction to the use of Arduino Development Plates 1 Applications with simple io modules 1 Using LCD display, use of interruption system 1 Use of timer 1 Communication interfaces 1 Serial Software communication interface."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Design with microprocessors evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing theoretical knowledge and a the ability to solve problems Written exam 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory Practical skills to solve and implementation of specific problems, of design design. Presence and activity Continuing laboratory evaluation, Continuous and final evaluation design 50 Design Minimum Performance Standard Modeling and implementing a typical engineering problem using the formal device characteristic of the domain."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in User interface design?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in User interface design?",
    "answer": "The basic methodology for developing software applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in User interface design?",
    "answer": "C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of User interface design?",
    "answer": "Study and experimentation of software development methodology methodology interactive. Study of human-calculator interaction techniques."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of User interface design?",
    "answer": "1. Apply User -oriented Software Development Methodology 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in User interface design?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Historical 2 Means are used multimedia of teaching at the course."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is User interface design evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note 44 course The written exam tests the understanding and the ability to apply knowledge acquired at the course. The activity at the course evaluates the participation Active students in discussions and analyzes from the course throughout the semester."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Logical design?",
    "answer": "The major objective of the discipline is the analysis and synthesis of numerical devices To allow students to analyze, design and implement numerical devices."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Logical design?",
    "answer": "To achieve the main goal, the specific objectives are pursued Analysis and synthesis of combinational logical systems Analysis and synthesis of synchronous and asynchronous logical logical systems Applying the principles of logical design and descriptive techniques Using programmable circuits to implement devices numerical Understanding temporal constraints in numerical systems and studying to them by simulation. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Logical design evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solving skills. Lack of test promotion score involves not admitting the exam."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Design methodologies, data structures, basic design templates"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation 24 their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives of Solution, to optimize performance. C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "The general objective of the discipline is the presentation and analysis of the solutions architectural on different levels of abstracting"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Identify the most relevant functional and non -functional requirements of a software system and document them Understanding the principles of design and packages design Analyze the software architectures in relation to the design principles known Recognize the fundamental architectural styles of software and Design models Design appropriate software architectures based on the given requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Classes design principles solid 2 Presentations, PowerPoint, quizs, themes and discussions, Course materials Moodle Classes design principles GRAP and packs 2 Architectural templates Layers, Event-Diven, MVC 2 Domain-Driven Design 2 Service-Oriented Design 2 Partial examcode demonstration 2 Sabloons applied in Enterprise Architects Access to Resources 2 Sabloons applied in Enterprise Architects presentation 2 Sabloons applied in Enterprise Architects Competition 2 Application of design creative design templates 2 Application of design structural design templates 2 Application of design behavioral design 2 Quality and metric attributes of the quality of software projects 2 Recapitulation and Preparation for the exam 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 34 Recapitulative exercises OOP, UML, test techniques. principles SOLID 3 IMPLEMENTATION OF themes on the systems from the laboratorygithub, presentations and demonstrations on the board Connection to specific databases and operations 3 Grasp."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Proiectare software evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Skills to understand the requirements, Analysis of alternative solutions and Design of the right solution, present, activity evaluation_curs Written exam, resolution quizs Moodle along the way P 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory Skills Analysis of Requirements and Solutions alternatives, design and implementation solution, presence, activity evaluation_labproject Laboratory themes, Github project 1-P. Design Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note P evaluation_curs 1-p evaluation_lab project Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory note 5 and project note 5 conditions promotion Discipline note 5, evaluation_curs 5 Date of completion 22.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Date database design?",
    "answer": "Lecturer dr. ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Date database design?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives of resolution, to optimize performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including the identification and analysis of the problem, Designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Date database design?",
    "answer": "The acquisition of general knowledge of the structures of databases related"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Date database design?",
    "answer": "Data base design - case studies in different base management systems Data MS SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle, Nosql, ... Presentation of procedural extensions of SQL language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Date database design?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations The first steps in designing databases data and information 2 History of database science types of databases 2 Business rules, data models hierarchical, entity-relation network, relational, object -oriented 2 Degrees of data abstraction the conceptual model the model internal external model physical model 2 Concepts and terminology of entity-relation entity-relation diagrams tables Relationships connectivity and cardinality, participation constraints Super-type and sub-type entities 2 Functional dependencies Normalization 2 SQL-Transact-SQL procedural extensions Storage procedures, trigger 2 SQL-Transact-SQL procedural extensions Storage procedures, trigger 2 Control of competing access, transactions Management transactions Journals, blockages Locks 2 Non -Relative Databases - Nosql 2 Mongodb 2 34 Data Warehouse - fields in which Business is required Intelligence, data analysis, support for taking a decisions, architectures 2 Facts, dimensions, attributes, hierarchs Date Mining 2 Administration of databases, security 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Alexandru Leluţiu - the concept of concepts promoted by the databases, ed."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Date database design?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Database Management System - Microsoft SQL Server 2 Design of database structures tables, keys, relationships 2 Design of database structures Index structures, Constraints, views 2 ETL - Extract transform Load 2 Simple stored procedures, functions 2 Stored procedures using cursor 2 Triggers trigger 2 Transactions 2 Database administration - MS SQL Server database database 2 Mongodb 2 Mongodb applications 2 Mongodb applications 2 NOSQL Non-Relative Databases 2 Final Laboratory Evaluation - Final Laboratory Evaluation 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Alexandru Leluţiu - the concept of concepts promoted by the databases, ed."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Date database design evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note The content of the discipline is in accordance with what is done in other university centers in the country and especially of abroad. My professional experience in commercial and university applications helps me adapt the content of the discipline to the requirements of the labor market."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Discipline Computer Networks Discipline"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "C3 - Solving Problems Using Science and Engineering tools COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of Solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - use of interdisciplinary knowledge, patterns of solutions and tools, conducting experiments and interpretation their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and engineering methods C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives of resolution, to optimize performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C5 - Designing, managing life cycle, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods to ensure security, safety and ease in operation of computing systems C5.4 - the appropriate use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Knowing how to operate a computer network"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Knowing network protocols and equipment Checking the functioning of a computer network Knowing the design stages of a network protocol"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction 2 ISO-OOSI and TCPIP reference model Models Presentation, comparison and analogies 2 Physical level functions of physical level 2 Data link level data link level functions, HDLC protocol 2 Network level network level functions and routing types 2 Transport level the functions of the transport level with connection and without connection 2 Upper levels features of session levels, presentation and application 2 Multiplexing Techniques FDM, TDM, Statistical TDM 2 Switching packages and virtual circuits analogies, differences and commutation 2 Flow control and Avoid Congestion Stop and Wait, Window sliding, the token bucket 2 The hierarchical model of designing a computer network Model Presentation and Equipment Selection 2 34 Security in computer networks the main attacks and prevention modes 2 Encryption systems used in computer networks systems symmetrical, asymmetrical systems 2 Elements of Computer Network Management The elements of a management app 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. A."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction, recap 2 Subneting and Superneting 2 Application level protocols 2 Vlan virtual networks, trunking 2 IPV6 IPV6 static routing 2 Dynamic routing 2 Easy IP DHCP, Nat 2 DNS 2 Security in computer networks 2 Network Inspector 2 Wireless networks 2 Voip 2 Chalange Lab 2 Laboratory colloquium 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. E."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Designing computer networks evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solving, presentation theoretical aspects Written exam, theory, problems Conditioned by the promotion Colloquium 40 30 Seminar - - - Laboratory Know and can set up equipment of network colloquy 30 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Minimum 70 presence in the course and 100 at the laboratory, has basic notions, can configure medium level equipment network. Calculation Discipline note 30 laboratory 70 Final exam Conditions of participation in the laboratory colloquium Presence at all laboratory hours, performing all laboratory Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 44 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Writing program in C What do I use operating system services"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying relevant life cycle criteria, The quality, security and interaction of the environmental computing system and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need quality."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Understanding the functionality of an operating system as a whole and a its components, such as the process manager, the memory manager, the file system."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "1. Knowing the different levels and components of a system of Operation, the role and functionality of each and the relationship between them."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Methods of rendition Observations The general structure of a SO. Possibilities of structuring a SO monolith, on levels, micro-carnel, virtual car, exokernel, Its components, their functionality and role, interconnection from they."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Methods of rendition Observations Introduction to the operating system used installation, compilation, tread, tESTING 2 1. Short presentations of the subject and MAIN key points 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Presentation SA used, theme and mode of work 1 Discussions with students on the edge themes taught, Highlighting Teaching and presentation Design mode threads 1 Teaching and presentation Implementation Threads mode 1 Teaching and presentation Design UserProg Mode 1 Teaching and presentation Implementation UserProg Mode 1 Teaching and presentation Design virtual-memory mode 1 Teaching and presentation implementation virtual-memory mode 1 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies Handbook of SO used, available on the Moodle page of the course at httpsmoodle.cs.utcluj.ro 45 9. Corroboration of the contents of the discipline with the expectations of the representatives of the epistemic community, the associations professional and representative employers in the field related to the program The course presents techniques for managing hardware and software resources by the operating system, but these They are valid in the case of any resources to be managed similar to another software level."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Designing operating systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Presence and activity at course hours The correctness of the answers to the topics of exam Knowing the alternatives of Design of the different components of a So ability to apply knowledge on concrete cases. Addressing questions, discussing some problems and Short tests at course hours Grid type exam on the platform Moodle and oral examination, based on discussing some concrete design issues of some components of a SO."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "logical design Knowing a high -level programming language C or Pascal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning components of hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation using hardware description languages hardware, software and communication components"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "The major objective of the discipline is to deepen the design and implementation numerical systems for obtaining performing numerical systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "To achieve the main goal, the specific objectives are pursued Use manual or automated tools, analyze or the performance of numerical systems under different conditions of operation To justify and optimize the chosen design solutions To implement, simulate and test in hardware description languages such as VHDL any numerical system To identify, design and make any type of numerical system."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Hardware circuits Implementing a system using FPGA technology Differences between asic vs fpga 3 Means multimedia - Power Point presentations - demonstrations on sheet - hours of consultations in the time of the semester and before each exam. NA VHDL hardware description language - generic parameters, Constant, operators, data types, attributes 3 VHDL hardware description language - sequential domain 3 VHDL hardware description language - Competitor 3 Creating test benches for circuit simulation and testing in VHDL 3 The theory of automatic state machines - classification, definitions, formal models 3 microprogramming 3 Microprogramate devices 3 Design of synchronous machines 3 Analysis and design of asynchronous machines I 3 Analysis and design of asynchronous machines II 3 Identification of machines 3 Loss -free cars 3 Linear automatons 3 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to VHDL. Fundamental design units."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Design of numerical systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course System design skills numeric. Lack of scoring to the laboratory involves non -admitting to the exam Written exam 60 Laboratory System design skills NUMBER The absences at the laboratory involve not admitting to the laboratory test."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Basic programming knowledge and data structures preferably in C and Javas languages - notions of generative grammatics and formal languages - Knowing the basic principles in designing interpreters and translators for artificial languages"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Design of translators?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying relevant life cycle criteria, quality, security and interaction of the calculation system with the environment and the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Knowing the phases of translators for programming languages lexical analysis, syntactic analysis and code generation. Knowing the phases of natural language processing and language models Bert."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Design of translators?",
    "answer": "To know the classes of languages for which they can be implemented efficient translators and interpreters. Know the rules of processing the typical instructions for interpreter."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Tools for representation Extended BNF notation. 2 35 2 Regular grammar and finite automatons finite automatons, diagrams of regular state and expressions."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Building descending syntactic analyzers recursively from Extended BNF grammar. 2 Short presentation at sheet card didactic, implementation and testing examples and computer exercises students."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Numerical coding of texts in natural language word bags Bow, TF-IDF and Bag of N-Gram. 2 Classifier of type feelings analyzer using logistical Regression lr."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Design of translators evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - Skills to solve it issues - presence, activity - evaluation along the course during the courses, through dialogue with students and exits to the board during courses - Consultations are organized before the exam, to which bonus is granted for the final exam - The final exam is written exam 44 Seminar - - - Laboratory - Skills to solve it issues - presence, activity Laboratory works - The evaluation of the activity of the students, every hour of laboratory - Bonus is awarded for the final exam Project laboratory sessions - The evaluation of the activity of the students, every hour of project laboratory 35 21 Design Minimum Performance Standard Modeling a typical engineering problem using the formal device characteristic of the Calculation Domain Discipline note 35 laboratory 21 project 44 final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Note 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing. Emil-Stefan Chifu Applications Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Project Management?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Project Management?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching Methods Notes - 33 Bibliography - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Project Preparing Methodology?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching Methods Notes - Bibliography - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 33"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "The control of concepts, theories, methods and principles of psychology education Understanding the essence and particularities of the learning process Knowing and understanding the methods and techniques of personality assessment STUDENT The control of the concepts, respectively of the methodology related to the development of the individual The correct understanding and use of the notions and principles regarding the processes cognitive and metacognitive involved in the learning process. Applying the principles and teaching methods specific to the activities taught disciplines to ensure students school progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "Efficient realization of activities and exercising specific roles in teamwork. - promoting the spirit of initiative, dialogue, cooperation, positive attitude and Respect for others, diversity and multiculturality and continuous improvement of ones own activity."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "COURSE acquiring foundations notional Looking dynamics and evolution Psycho -behavioral students capitalizing on knowledge accumulated in Elaboration of some products observation sheet, modification tools behavior, formulating educational goals in accordance with effective learning ways, which may indicate capabilities of analysis, synthesis, Student application, interpretation and thinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "1. formation of the ability to analyze and evaluate the learning process 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "Teaching methods Observations Introduction to educational psychology Interactive course - exposure - intensified lecture - the explanation - heuristic conversation Adaptation the concept of adaptation and its forms. stances adaptation."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "Teaching methods Observations Educational psychology principles, goals, methods - problematization - tutorial - exercises - debate - case study - the discussion of the reports Psychological methods of investigating the student and class experimentally, the correlational study The personality traits of the competent teacher Using stories in teaching and learning The theory of processing information and learning in school simulation, debate The constructivist paradigm for learning in school tutorial, case study Modalities of application of learning principles in the process of Teaching design - Application Conceptual Map Learning techniques Cognitive-behavioral techniques of performance improvement school Development of moral personality - moral dilemmas The stadium development of the personality Jurcău, N. coord 2008."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Psychology of education evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course Solving problems and answers For topics in theory final examination 60. Seminarlaboratory Presentation of essays and case studies Essays 40 Minimum performance standard to solve topics corresponding to the minimum grade 5."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Physics electricity, basic knowledge in programming languages C, Java, C, Python Computer architecture, operating systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Computer networks?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metrics C2.5 - Implementation of hardware systems components, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer networks?",
    "answer": "The major objective of the discipline is the introductory presentation of the main types of communications networks, to allow students to analyze, design and implements the interconnection of computers in a network and interconnection networks. Team work, working with partial specifications and CONFLICTING"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Each student is able to design software and hardware architecture a Lan. To achieve the main goal, the specific objectives are pursued Basic elements in data transmission theory The main types of local networks Knowing the architecture of the Internet Knowing the main services on the Internet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Concepts, types of computer networks, Characteristics, evolution, standardization 2 Exposure to the board, Slide presentation, Discussions Q A, Consultations."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Laboratory presentation Elements of labor protection Introduction In computer networks 2 Practical works, Software use and equipment Specific, presentation Slides, discussions Q a Introduction to Wireshark and Cisco Packet Tracer 2 Copper -based transmission media 2 Transmission media based on fiber optics 2 Structured wiring 2 Network connection IPV4 foundations 2 Network connection IPV4 Routing and DHCP 2 Network login IPV6 2 Application Level Network programming using sockets 2 Ethernet, ARP and NDP 2 Vlans, trunking and routing inter-vlan 2 Level 2 networks, Spanning Tree Protocol, Link Aggregation and Ethererchannel 2 Security threats in computer networks 2 Laboratory test 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. A."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Computer networks evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing theoretical knowledge skills of problem solving Presence, activity Written exam 60 Laboratory Problem solving skills Presence, activity Laboratory test 40 44 Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final Conditions Exam of participation in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 03.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Vasile Dădârlat Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Operation with scientific and computer foundations"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "C5 - Maintenance and exploitation of hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Identification and description of modeling, simulation and instruments Evaluation of the performance of the hardware, software and communications C5.2 - Using interdisciplinary knowledge for insurance exploitation of hardware, software and communications systems in relation to The requirements of the field of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance Security, safety and ease of exploitation of hardware systems, software and communications C5.4 - Qualitative testing and evaluation of functional characteristics and non -functional computer systems, based on specific criteria C5.5 - Development of systems and applications for maintenance and use of hardware, software and communications systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Knowing the concepts, applications and technologies for security systems and software. Acquiring the ability to contribute constructively to analysis, evaluation and design of safe systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Understanding the fundamental components related to the security of the systems, a risks related to their use, vulnerabilities and threats important. Active participation in identifying and analyzing issues of computer security."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations General security concepts 2 Exposure, discussions, projector Defensive programming I 2 Defensive programming II 2 Defensive programming III 2 Introduction to cryptography. Transposition and substitution."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Programs analysis C. 2 Outings of the area allocated 2 33 Vulnerabilities of format strings 2 Exposure and applications Computers, software of programming, software cryptographic, MACHINERY virtual Vulnerability due to competition 2 Vulnerability of type exceeding memory area 2 Secret key figure 2 Cryptography with public key and pki 2 The Shellshock attack 4 DNS attacks 4 Attacks against web servers 4 ASSESSMENT 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The security of systems and applications evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Active participation in class hours Written exam 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Active participation in laboratory work Analysis and notation of results applications 50 Minimum Performance Standard The correct resolution of 60 of the exam topics and laboratory themes. Calcutta Discipline note 50 Final exam 50 Laboratory Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Note 5 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Şl.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "Creative combination of different modern research and development principles of interdisciplinary fields with computer components"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - The use of interdisciplinary knowledge, the patterns of solutions and of tools, carrying out experiments and interpreting results their C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and methods ENGINEERING C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives resolution, for the optimization of performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Designing intelligent systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - use of domain specific tools for Explaining and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "Familiarize with different technical instrumentation for representation knowledge and reasoning on them. It aims to increase the ability to Model reality and choose adequate technical instrumentation for the current problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "To achieve these general objectives, the students will 1. Learn to apply methods of representing knowledge to scenarios practical 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Introduction."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Knowledge graphs."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Knowledge -based systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course The ability to identify and formula problems in the real world The ability of to build models for problems specific Critical analysis capacity Written exam, partial evaluation 60 Seminar The ability to argue and support technical opinions The ability to choose Technical instrumentation appropriate to a specific problems Technical and scientific presentation of to an article 10 Laboratory Creativity Compliance with terms The ability to represent and query of knowledge The ability to identify advantages and disadvantages of the solution proposed The ability to work in the team Oral presentation of ontology developed 30 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Understanding the description logic and logic. The engineering of decent ontology."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "Design templates, software architectures"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "C5 - maintenance and operation of hardware, software and communications C5.1 - Identification and description of modeling, simulation and instruments Evaluation of the performance of the hardware, software and communications C5.2 - Using interdisciplinary knowledge for insurance exploitation of hardware, software and communications systems in relation to The requirements of the field of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance Security, safety and ease of exploitation of hardware systems, software and communications C5.4 - Qualitative testing and evaluation of functional characteristics and non -functional computer systems, based on specific criteria C5.5 - Development of systems and applications for maintenance and use of hardware, software and communications systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "The course objective is the familiarization with modern evaluation techniques of quality and reliability of software systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "In order to achieve the general goal, the specific objectives are pursued Understanding the need for quality. Studying test methods."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Software quality. Quality attributes 2 Exposure systematic Examples Discussions Estimating the cost of a software product 2 Domain management."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 33 - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified. 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Quality systems in TI evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course Problem solving skills, activity. Written evaluation 100 Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Conditions of promotion Final note 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Şl.dr.info."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Inputoutput systems and peripheral equipment?",
    "answer": "Knowing the operation and performance parameters of some interfaces of inputoutput and peripheral equipment the skill of communication with the controllers of the peripheral equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Inputoutput systems and peripheral equipment?",
    "answer": "Applying the basic methods and principles for growth the performance of the calculation systems Designing inputoutput interfaces for connecting some equipment at a computer Design and program implementation of protocols of inputexit Writing system programs for interface control of entryoutput. 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Inputoutput systems and peripheral equipment evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note Understanding some theoretical concepts of Check tests at classes 10 44 course inputoutput systems and a the principle of operating some of some peripheral equipment Written exam 50 Laboratory Skills of writing programs of communication with the controllers of some peripheral equipment Checking the mode of Solving the proposed applications at laboratory sessions and Laboratory colloquium 40 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Presence at each laboratory session Completion of a minimum of an app at each laboratory session Calculation Discipline note 10 Verification tests 40 laboratory 50 Conditions exam of participation in the final exam Verification tests 5, laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion exam 5 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Zoltan-Franisc Baruch Applications Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Programming in C language"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of performance hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing evaluation criteria and methods The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware, software and of communications based on the increase of performance"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Assimilating the fundamental concepts of operating systems, understanding the role of the operating system within a calculation system, analyzing the mode General operating system operating and ability to use calls System for programming the operating system."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Knowing and understanding the terminology specific to operating systems, Understanding the functionality and general structure of operating systems, Understanding how the operating system manages resources system execution management, memory management, management peripheral devices. Understanding the mechanisms and policies of planning and synchronization of execution and development of the ability to use these mechanisms for solving some problems in the real world, Practical understanding and application of system calls within the development applications in language C."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. The general role of a SO."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Presentation of SO Laboratory purpose, content, strategies, Requirements, regulation. Familiarizing with Linux operating system Linux file system, basic orders 2 Orally and by means multimedia Teaching style Interactive, resolution of problems tests of evaluation and discussion solutions homework Miniprocts NA System calls for access to file data 2 System calls for work and directors in Linux 2 Calls System for Process Management 2 System calls for thread management 2 Processes and Threads Management 2 Synchronization mechanisms traffic lights 2 Synchronization mechanisms locks and conditional variables 2 Communication Mechanisms Pipe files with name and anonym 2 Communication mechanisms shared memory and map files 2 Recapitulation mechanisms of communication and synchronization 2 Aspects related to Code security 2 REVIEW 2 colloquy 2 Bibliography 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Sisteme de operare evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Testing theoretical knowledge and a the ability to solve some problems on the basis of knowledge from operating systems. Written exam 60 Laboratory Testing the resolution skills on computer of problems using L Linux system and call calls."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Forms?",
    "answer": "Programming, data structures and algorithms, probability theory, analysis linear, artificial intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Forms?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications 24 C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - use of domain specific tools for Explaining and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying of solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Forms?",
    "answer": "Knowledge, understanding and use of concepts related to recognition forms."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Forms?",
    "answer": "Knowledge, understanding and use of recognition methods based on Model using statistical approaches, linearly discriminant methods, support vectors, assembly of classifiers. Knowledge, understanding and use of specific operations of a system of Form recognition Preprocessing data, reducing size, Selection of relevant features, building the prediction model, selection The optimal model, performance assessment."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Forms?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction 1 General decoration of a system of recognition of forms. 2 Orally and by means multimedia, style Interactive teaching, Consultations, involvement students in activities Design."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Forms evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course Testing the Toretic knowledge and a problem solving skills Written exam 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory Practical skills to solve and Implementation of problems and of Design specific applications. Presence and activity Colloquium, project evaluation 50 Design Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 25 Laboratory 25 Project 50 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5, project 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 10.06.2024 titular Title First Name course Şl.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "The ability to analyze and design a local network, using simulators available. The ability to design an application using Layed architectures."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and Communications 2 credits C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems 2 credits C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems 1 credit C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "The ability to develop and implement distributed sophware systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "The ability to design distributed systems at the architectural level and by components using the main concepts and paradigms of the systems distributed as well as their relationships with other disciplines in computer science. - The ability to identify the main models and technologies that can be used in the design of the distributed systems being given a set of constraints."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to distributed systems, characterization of systems Distributed 2 Use of methods multimedia of teaching and access to the Internet Students are invited to Collaborate on projects of cores of lectureship Hours of consultations in the time of the semester and before the exam Case study of Google data centers 2 The quality of services, non-functional aspects of systems Distributed, metric 2 Communication paradigms between processes 2 Entities that communicate in distributed systems customer-server, peer to Peer 2 Organization and computational model distributed 2 Time and causality, logical watches 2 Global states, snapshots, distributed algorithms 2 Distributed data processing - concepts and architecture of reference 2 Data distribution techniques 2 Management of distributed transactions 2 Competition control 2 Basic concepts in the cloud computing 2 Calculatory -based calculation systems 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. G."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Basic concepts in developing Spring distributed applications, React 4 laboratory sessions 8 Themes and examples predefined. Short presentation of lab themes, Based discussions themes, implementation the themes on the computer, individual miniproject on the computer Tool for continuous integration, test and deployment a PROJECT Asynchronous communication RabbitMQ 2 laboratory sessions 4 Distributed objects GRPC 4 laboratory sessions 8 Presentations, discussions and evaluation of students themes 4 sessions of laboratory 8 Project Docker, Cloud Computing, CICD, Basic Security, UTC Time 6 Development and integration of services 3 Deployment using docker 3 Evaluation of student projects 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Distributed systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The degree of assimilation of knowledge about distributed systems taught within COURSE Written exam 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory -The capacity to design systems distributed at the architectural level and by components using the main concepts and paradigms of distributed systems as well as their relationships with other disciplines in Computer science -Capacity to identify the main models and technologies that can be used in Design of distributed systems being given a set of constraints -presence, activity Evaluation Laboratory Works and design The tool for integration Continue, Deployment and Testing of distributed applications 35 15 Design Minimum Performance Standard To be able to design and implement distributed software systems Calculation Discipline note 35 laboratory 15 project 50 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5, project 5 -timely preparation of all laboratory works and minimum grade 5 per work present at at least 11 works of laboratory Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 04.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Tudor Cioara Applications Şl.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Application of principle and basic methods for specifying solutions to Typical problems using smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "C6 - Design of Expert Systems C6.1 - Description of Expert Systems Components C6.2 - the use of domain specific tools for explanation and Understanding the operation of expert systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying Solutions to typical problems using expert systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, Experts performance and limits C6.5 - Development and implementation of projects professional for expert systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Knowing the formalisms of representation of knowledge and reasoning in the field of expert systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "To achieve these general objectives, students will learn - to represent the knowledge in logical or unexacted form probabilistic, shade - to rat based on exact or inaccurate rules - to choose the most appropriate way of representing knowledge and reason for the given issue - to develop a functional expert system"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction definition, components, evolution, applicability, 2 Physical exposure on Base of slides, discussions and questions short Expert systems examples Knowledge representation semantic networks, object triplets- 2 attribute-value. Knowledge representation logic, production rules."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to the clips. Facts and rules."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Sisteme expert evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course Problems Testing the acquisition of notions of the base Final exam - Physical Written exam test Moodle 40 Seminar - - - Laboratory Knowing the development instruments of expert systems the ability to develop an application using these TOOLS Laboratory exam - Physical Written lab test The problem on your computer test Moodle quiz problem on computer Project evaluation 25 lab Design 35 project Minimum Performance Standard Knowing the theoretical tools and technologies necessary to develop an expert system the ability to analyze, Design and implement an expert system using fairly chosen technologies. Calculation Discipline note 25 laboratory 35 project 40 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5, project 5 Conditions of promotion Note 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "The ability to analyze and design a local network, using simulators available. The ability to design an application using Layed architectures."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and Communications 2 credits C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems 2 credits C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems 1 credit C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "The ability to design distributed systems at the architectural level and by components using the main concepts and paradigms of the systems distributed as well as their relationships with other disciplines in computer science. - The ability to identify the main models and technologies that can be used in the design of the distributed systems, a set of constraints was given."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to distributed systems, characterization of systems Distributed 2 Use methods multimedia of teaching and access to the Internet Students are invited saddle contributor TO Research projects of the reader Hours of consultations in the time of the semester and before the exam Case study of Google data centers 2 The quality of services, non-functional aspects of systems Distributed, metric 2 Communication paradigms between processes 2 Entities that communicate in distributed systems customer-server, peer to Peer 2 Organization and computational model distributed 2 Time and causality, logical watches 2 Global states, snapshots, distributed algorithms 2 Distributed data processing - concepts and architecture of reference 2 Data distribution techniques 2 Management of distributed transactions 2 Competition control 2 Basic concepts in the cloud computing 2 Calculatory -based calculation systems 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. G."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Basic concepts in the development of distributed applications Spring, react 4 laboratory sessions 8 Themes and examples PREDEFINED Short presentation of lab themes, discussions based on themes, IMPLEMENTATION OF the themes on the computer, individual miniproject on the computer Tool for continuous integration, test and deployment a PROJECT Asynchronous communication RabbitMQ 2 laboratory sessions 4 Distributed objects GRPC 4 laboratory sessions 8 Presentations, discussions and evaluation of students themes 4 meetings of laboratory 8 Project Docker, Cloud Computing, CICD, Basic Security, UTC Time 6 Development and integration of services 3 Deployment using docker 3 Evaluation of student projects 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Ioan Salomie, Tudor Cioara, Ionut Anghel, Tudor Salomie - Distributed Computing and Systems - A Practical Approach, Blue Publ."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Sisteme Informatice Distribuite evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course The degree of assimilation of knowledge about distributed systems taught within COURSE Written exam 50 Seminar - - - Laboratory - the ability to design systems distributed at the architectural level and by components using the main concepts and paradigms of distributed systems as well as their relationships with other disciplines in Computer science - the ability to identify the main models and technologies that can be used in Design of distributed systems being given a set of constraints - presence, activity Evaluation Laboratory Works and design The tool for integration Continue, Deployment and Testing of distributed applications 35 15 Design Minimum Performance Standard - To be able to designed and implement distributed software systems Calculation Discipline note 35 laboratory 15 project 50 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5, project 5 - Time teaching of all laboratory works and minimum grade 5 per work present at at least 11 works laboratory - In a session outstanding a student can teach 1 laboratory theme or 1 project unfinished during the semester. Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Date of completion 07.06.2024 titular First name Signature course Şl.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme informatice?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth 23 The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase C5 - design, life cycle management, integration and integrity hardware, software and communications systems C5.1 - Specifying the relevant criteria regarding the life cycle, quality, the security and interaction of the system of calculation with the environment and with the human operator C5.2 - Use of interdisciplinary knowledge for adaptation The computer system in relation to the requirements of the area of applications C5.3 - Use of basic principles and methods for insurance security, safety and ease of operation of computing systems C5.4 - the proper use of quality standards, safety and security in information processing C5.5 - carrying out a project including identification and analysis the problem, designing, developing and demonstrating an understanding of the need for quality C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - Use of domain specific tools for explanation And understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme informatice?",
    "answer": "Design of computer systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme informatice?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Management management 2 Video presentations BRUS - review and recommendations 2 Rupt - iterative development 2 Discipline of Requirements according to RUP 2 Capture of functional requirements Cases of use i 2 Capture of functional requirements Cases of use II - recommendation 2 Artifacts of the analysis model vision, glossary, specification Additional i 2 Artifacts of the analysis model vision, glossary, specification Additional ii 2 Building a domain model 2 Grasp Design Patterns I 2 Grasp Design Patterns II 2 Cases of use using Grasp Design Patterns I 2 Cases of use using Grasp Design Patterns II 2 Cases of use using GRAP Design Patterns III 2 Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which 33 exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Craig Larman - Applying Uml and Patterns 2003 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Sisteme informatice?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Artifacts of the discipline of requirements vision, glossary, specification SUPPLEMENTARY 4 Generating a vision document based on a RUP template 4 Generating an additional specification document based on an template break 4 Artifacts of the Requirement Discipline Cases of use 4 Generating a case document of use based on a template OR 4 Generating a model of analysis 4 Individual evaluation of the activity submitted 4 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1. Craig Larman - Applying Uml and Patterns 2003 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Sisteme informatice evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Theoretical knowledge problems Written exam 90 Seminar - - - Laboratory Application of theoretical knowledge Evaluation generated artifacts 10 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Laboratory Teaching Theoretical Knowledge Calculation Discipline note 100 exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion note 5 Note Students who shared less than 50 of the courses presented do not have the right to formulate applications Referring to how they are evaluated Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing. Ovidiu Pop Applications Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Fundamental programming elements, discrete mathematics, analysis mathematics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "C6 - Design of smart systems C6.1 - Description of intelligent systems components C6.2 - the use of domain specific tools for explanation and understanding the functioning of smart systems C6.3 - Applying the basic principles and methods for specifying solutions to typical problems using intelligent systems C6.4 - Choosing the criteria and methods of quality assessment, the performances and limits of intelligent systems C6.5 - Development and implementation of professional projects for smart systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Knowing the representation of intelligent systems and reasoning on them"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Introduction."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations 1. Learning with decision -making trees."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Sisteme Inteligente evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Specific problems and tools Exam moodle 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory The exploitation and evaluation of the instruments clever 2 interests Moodle 40 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The ability to be able to draw specific algorithms. The ability to model realistic scenarios."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Software design?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Special Mathematics I?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "The skills of the logical design disciplines, the architecture of the computers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "C2 - Design of hardware, software and communications components C2.1 - Description of the structure and functioning of hardware components, software and communications C2.2 - Explanation of the role, interaction and functioning of the components hardware, software and communications systems C2.3 - Construction of hardware, software and Communications using methods of design, languages, algorithms, structures of data, protocols and technologies C2.4 - Evaluation of the functional and non -functional characteristics of hardware, software and communications components, based on some Metra C2.5 - Implementation of hardware, software and communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "Knowing the structure of some components of the calculation systems and the skills designing these components"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "Design and hardware implementation of arithmetic operations with whole numbers and in a mobile comma Design of hierarchical memory systems and cache memoirs Using the pipeline technique and systolic matrices for implementing with high performance of arithmetic operations Designing and implementing hardware modules on different plates of development with FPGA circuits using VHDL language Knowing the main parallel computing architectures and directions currents in the field of computing architects."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Obs. Introduction."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Obs. Measurement of computer systems performance with benchmarks 2 34 CPU performance monitoring using the Time-Stamp Counter register 2 - Explanations ADDITIONAL - applications on plates of Circuit development Fpga - the use of one development environment for FPGA circuits NA Programming items in VHDL 2 Design of ALU components 2 FPGA synthesis 2 Introduction to the use of Microcontroller Picoblaze with Nexys3 plate 2 Implementation of a MIPS processor in VHDL -1 2 Implementation of a MIPS processor in VHDL - 2 2 Implementation of a mips pipeline processor 2 Memory design - 1 2 Memory design - 2 2 Advanced hardware design techniques 2 Design implementations on Nexys 3 plate 2 Laboratory colloquium 2 Bibliography 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is The structure of the calculation systems evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Understanding of theoretical concepts, skills to solve some problems Written exam 60 Laboratory Solving the topics proposed to laboratory sessions Checking the way of solving a themes proposed at meetings of Laboratory and written colloquium 20 Design Designing, implementing and testing hardware modules Evaluation of project phases, Presentation of written documentation and Supporting a practical demonstration for the insured project 20 Minimum Performance Standard Presence at each laboratory session Solving the themes proposed at Laboratory Meetings Calculation Discipline note 20 laboratory 20 project 60 exam Participation conditions in the final exam, laboratory 5, project 5, written exam 5 Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 Date of completion 05.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Prof.dr.ing. Gheorghe Sebestyen Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "Computer programming C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with mathematical, engineering and computer foundations C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, software and communications C1.3 - building models for different components of computing systems C1.4 - Formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "The major objective of the discipline is the knowledge and processing of type structures List, tree, graph and dispersion table and general methods of elaboration of algorithm"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "The following goals are pursued to reach the stated object Specific a operations on the simple and double -chained dynamic lists b operations on binary trees c representation in memory of the graphs, crossing algorithms d operations on a dispersion table e presentation of general methods of elaboration of algorithms Greedy, backtracking, divide et impera etc. f vector sorting algorithms."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction objectives, recommended bibliography. Solving problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Presentation of works, programming environment and requirements at laboratory 2 Presence at the laboratory mandatory. Solution on computer of some problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Data structures and algorithms evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Problem solving skills theoretical and writing of algorithms in pseudo Written exam Written tests 60 10 44 Seminar - - - Laboratory Computer resolution skills a issues 2 practical tests, on the computer, along the semester 30 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard The knowledge and implementation of the fundamental operations on the lists, trees, graphs and dispersion tables and the general methods of developing algorithms. Calculation Discipline note 30 Laboratory 60 Final exam 10 course written tests Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Final exam 5 Written exam, problem solving."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Graduates will have the following specific skills Sub-system software and hardware modeling and hardware design by taking the optimal decision from the point of view of the cost-benefit ratio implementing a hardware or software system analyzing how the calculation system realizes the requirements for which was conceived as well as the proposal for improvements and developments subsequent demonstrating the knowledge and understanding of the main concepts, a principles and theory of computer science and engineering Identifying and analyzing specific problems as well as elaboration to strategies to solve them Ensuring the quality of products in the field of information technology Using Information Technology tools"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supporting the license work."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a proper number of copies The bibliography required by the preparation of the license work given at the Supervisor Recommendation Study products references specifications obtained from bibliographic study Review of the fundamental and specific knowledge obtained during the university years of study. The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Support of diploma project evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - presentation and support of the license work - evaluation of fundamental knowledge and specific Minimum Performance Standard N 6 33 Date of completion 10.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course - Applications Supervisor License Project Date of approval in the Computer Department Council 20.02.2024 Director of Department, Prof.dr.ing. Rodica Potolea Date of approval in the Faculty of Automation and Computers Council 22.02.2024 Dean, Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor License Project"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Graduates will have the following specific skills Sub-system software and hardware modeling and hardware design by taking the optimal decision from the point of view of the cost-benefit ratio Implementing a hardware or software system Analyzing how the calculation system realizes the requirements for which was conceived as well as the proposal for improvements and developments subsequent Demonstrating the knowledge and understanding of the main concepts, a principles and theory of computer science and engineering Identifying and analyzing specific problems as well as elaboration to strategies to solve them Ensuring the quality of products in the field of information technology Using Information Technology tools"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supporting the license work."
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography the minimum bibliography of the discipline containing at least one bibliographic work of reference, which exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies -"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations - Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline which exists available to students in a proper number of copies The bibliography required by the preparation of the license work given at the Supervisor Recommendation Study products references specifications obtained from bibliographic study Review of the fundamental and specific knowledge obtained during the university years of study. The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Support of diploma project evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course - - - Seminar - - - Laboratory - - - Design - presentation and support of the license work - evaluation of fundamental knowledge and specific 100 Minimum Performance Standard N 6 33 Date of completion 11.06.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course - Applications Supervisor License Project Date of approval in the Computer Department Council 20.02.2024 Director of Department, Prof.dr.ing. Rodica Potolea Date of approval in the Faculty of Automation and Computers Council 22.02.2024 Dean, Prof.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "Object -oriented programming knowledge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "C4 - improving the performance of hardware, software and communications C4.1 - Identification and description of defining elements of The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.2 - Explanation of the interaction of the factors that determine the performances hardware, software and communications systems C4.3 - Applying the basic methods and principles for growth The performances of the hardware, software and communications systems C4.4 - Choosing performance criteria and methods hardware, software and communications systems C4.5 - Development of professional solutions for hardware systems, software and communications based on performance increase"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "Knowing and applying object -oriented programming techniques in Development of software applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "To be able to use programming techniques for classes design and interfaces, including contracts and invariant - To be able to use programming techniques to reuse the code using inheritance and polymorphism - To be able to use generic-based programming techniques and streams for processing collections - To be able to use programming techniques for reflection, design patterns and Framework for reusing design solutions - To apply solid design principles and threads in java - Can use programming techniques for reflection and based on event - To be able to use programming-oriented and functional programming techniques in a Integrated approach for the development of flexible and efficient programs - To be able to use Lambda expressions and be able to perform processing operations of streams"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction - the process of software development and paradigms of appointment 2 - use of methods multimedia of teaching and Internet access - presentation of the courses and discussions. - questions addressed students during the course."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction - Resources and Requirements for Laboratory 2 Short presentation of lab themes, Discussions based on themes, Implementation of themes on the computer, discussions and evaluations. NA Theme 1 - programming techniques with inheritance and polymorphism 4 Theme 2 - Programming techniques with execution yarn 4 Theme 3 - Database programming techniques, pattern design- hats and reflection techniques 6 Theme 4 - programming techniques with Java Collection Framework, Lambda expressions and stream processing 6 Laboratory evaluation 4 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies - Online httpdocs.orracle.comjavaseturialindex.html httpstackoverflow.com The topic of seminars, laboratory works, the theme and stages of the project will be specified."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course Knowing and using the techniques of programming presented during the courses presence and interaction within courses. Written exam."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - The use of interdisciplinary knowledge, the patterns of solutions and of tools, carrying out experiments and interpreting results their C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and methods ENGINEERING C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives resolution, for the optimization of performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "Identifying some classes of problems and characteristic solving methods multimedia systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "Developing specific multimedia applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction. Historical."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Menus and tools in the Gimp. Purchase and import of images."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Multimedia technologies evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The degree of acquisition of theoretical knowledge Exam 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory The degree of acquisition of practical skills specific and completing the laboratory themes Evaluation along the way through themes to each laboratory 40 Design - - - 44 Minimum Performance Standard Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Note 5 Date of completion 23.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Şl.dr.ing. Cornelia Melenti Applications Şl.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "Operation with scientific, engineering and computer foundations"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "C3 - solving problems using the tools of science and engineering COMPUTER C3.1 - Identifying some classes of problems and methods of solving characteristic of computer systems C3.2 - The use of interdisciplinary knowledge, the print patterns and a tools, conducting experiments and interpreting their results C3.3 - Applying the patterns of solutions using tools and methods ENGINEERING C3.4 - Comparative evaluation, including experimental, alternatives resolution, for the optimization of performance C3.5 - Development and implementation of computer solutions for concrete problems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "The main objective of this discipline is to provide specific information and to prepare students to carry out projects using wireless technology. Thus, the aim is to confer the ability to analyze, design and implement Wireless networks and support for mobility."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "Assimilating theoretical knowledge on wireless networks Obtaining skills for designing and implementing networks wireless Assimilating theoretical knowledge on securing wireless networks Obtaining skills to implement security in wireless networks Assimilating theoretical knowledge regarding mobility in networks of computers Obtaining skills for implementing support for mobility in computer networks"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to wireless and mobile systems. Features, presentation 2 Interactive lecture, demonstration with help the video projector and of the table, questions and Discussions general, basic notions Physical level in wireless networks."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Foundations rf 2 Demonstration at board, questions and discussions simulation using Specific software Configuring wireless devices and mobile programming mobile devices RF 2 Connecting to the network 2 Wireless signal analysis Fluke Etherscope Series II Network Assistant and Aicheck G2 2 Wireless signal analysis Fluke Analyze-air 2 Design of wireless networks I Basic configurations 2 Design of wireless networks II Advanced configurations 2 Design of wireless networks III VPN configuration 2 Programming techniques in wireless networks 2 Security in wireless and mobile networks 2 Mobile devices foundations 2 Mobile devices programming techniques 2 Site Planning and Project Management 2 Laboratory test. 2 Bibliography minimal bibliography for applications containing at least one bibliographic work of the discipline that exists available to students in a corresponding number of copies 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Wireless technologies and mobile devices evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the final note course The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Presence, inter activity during hours of the course Written exam andor oral 60 Seminar - - - Laboratory The ability to solve some problems specific to the domain Presence, activity during hours of laboratory Written exam andor oral 40 Design - - - Minimum Performance Standard Design and configuration of wireless networks and mobility support. Calculation Discipline note 40 Laboratory 60 Final exam Participation conditions in the final exam Laboratory 5 Conditions of promotion Discipline note 5 Date of completion 28.05.2024 titular Title First Name Signature course Conf.dr.ing."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Systems theory?",
    "answer": "Differential equations, complex numbers, transformed laplace, linear algebra"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Systems theory?",
    "answer": "C1 - Operation with mathematical, engineering and computer foundations 24 C1.1 - Recognition and description of the concepts of the calculation, complexity, programming paradigms and modeling of systems of systems calculation and communications C1.2 - The use of specific theories and tools algorithms, schemes, models, protocols, etc. to explain the structure and functioning hardware, software and communications systems C1.3 - building models for different components of computing systems C1.4 - Formal evaluation of functional and non -functional characteristics of the calculation systems C1.5 - Theoretical foundation of the characteristics of the designed systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Systems theory?",
    "answer": "The general objective of the discipline is to introduce the fundamental principles of Modeling for automatic linear systems analysis and control and assessment negative reaction systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Systems theory?",
    "answer": "Specific goals refer to getting knowledge and skills related to - Mathematical modeling of systems differential equations, input representation- exit as transfer functions, models in the space space, block schemes for simple applications - Analysis of linear systems assessment of stability and performers of systems linear in the field of time and frequency - Design of automatic regulators such as PID, Lead-Lag, for systems linear, and design techniques in state space - Representation and analysis of sampling systems"
  },
  {
    "question": "What topics are covered in Systems theory?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to systems theory and automatic control. Introduction in Modeling of systems."
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of applications are practiced in Systems theory?",
    "answer": "Hours Teaching methods Observations Introduction to Matlab. Simulation of systems 4 Exercises solved using software specialized Matlab explanations additional discussions."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Systems theory evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity Evaluation criteria Evaluation methods Weight from the note final course The ability to solve exercises related to modeling and analysis of linear systems. The ability to solve exercises related to the projection of automatic systems and with sampling."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Volunteering 1357?",
    "answer": "Competes NTE According to the specificity of each faculty Transverse skills 1. Communication in the mother tongue - the ability to express and interpret concepts, thoughts, Feelings, facts and opinions, both in oral and written form obedience, speech, reading and writing and interacting linguistically in an adequate and creative way in a complete series of cultural and social contexts 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Volunteering 1357?",
    "answer": "COURSE Acquiring soft skills in non -formal and informal education contexts through voluntary involvement in activities within organizations non -governmental. Increasing employee of development by development of Compatible skills with the labor market Improve the quality of work of volunteer or as a preceding step for carrying out more activities volunteering complexes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Volunteering 1357?",
    "answer": "1. Knowledge and understanding the proper knowledge and use of discipline -specific notions understanding the relevance of the activity of volunteering in the context of the specialization profile followed Highlighting the particularities of the different non -governmental organizations as a whole society Understanding MODE of FUNCTIONING organizations Nonguvernamenale public from Romania from the perspective of regulations legal in force."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Volunteering 1357?",
    "answer": "Bibliography A. Good practice models or relevant projects carried out at European level and targeted Significant components centered on the recognition of competences developed by volunteering 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Volunteering 1357 evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity 10.1. Evaluation criteria 10.2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What skills are developed in Volunteer 2468?",
    "answer": "Competes NTE According to the specificity of each faculty Transverse skills 1. Communication in the mother tongue - the ability to express and interpret concepts, thoughts, Feelings, facts and opinions, both in oral and written form obedience, speech, reading and writing and interacting linguistically in an adequate and creative way in a complete series of cultural and social contexts 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Volunteer 2468?",
    "answer": "COURSE Acquiring soft skills in non -formal and informal education contexts through voluntary involvement in activities within organizations non -governmental. Increasing employee of development by development of Compatible skills with the labor market Improve the quality of work of volunteer or as a preceding step for carrying out more activities volunteering complexes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the objectives of Volunteer 2468?",
    "answer": "1. Knowledge and understanding the proper knowledge and use of discipline -specific notions understanding the relevance of the activity of volunteering in the context of the specialization profile followed Highlighting the particularities of the different non -governmental organizations as a whole society Understanding MODE of FUNCTIONING organizations Nonguvernamenale public from Romania from the perspective of regulations legal in force."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the content of Volunteer 2468?",
    "answer": "Bibliography A. Good practice models or relevant projects carried out at European level and targeted Significant components centered on the recognition of competences developed by volunteering 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "How is Volunteer 2468 evaluated?",
    "answer": "Type activity 10.1. Evaluation criteria 10.2."
  },
    {
    "question": "Who teaches the Administration of databases?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Delia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Administration of computer networks?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Emil Cebuc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Administration of operating systems?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Ciprian Oprișa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Linear algebra and analytical geometry?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Radu Peter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Algoritmi fundamentali?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Rodica Potolea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Mathematics I (differential calculation) analysis?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Dorian Popa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Analog and digital circuits?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Bogdan Iancu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Entrepreneurship?",
    "answer": "Dr.ec. Simona Sabo Martis , simona.martis@staff.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computers architecture?",
    "answer": "Prof.dr. ing. Florin Oniga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Groza Adrian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Assembly Language Programming?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Emil Cebuc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Baze de Date?",
    "answer": "CD asoc. ing. Cosmina Ivan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the The basis of quantum information?",
    "answer": "CS1 Dr.  Liviu Zarbo – liviu.zarbo@itim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Parallel and distributed?",
    "answer": "CD asoc. ing. Cosmina Ivan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Analog and numerical circuits?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Adrian Peculea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Communication protocols and networks project?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Emil Cebuc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer Architecture?",
    "answer": "Prof.dr.eng. Florin Oniga – Florin.Oniga@cs.utcluj.ro \nAssoc.prof.dr.eng.  Mihai Negru – Mihai.Negru@cs.utcluj.ro \nLect.dr.eng. Cristian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer Assisted Graphics?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Gorgan Dorian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer Network Design?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Emil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Vasile Dădârlat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer Programming?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Marius Joldoş"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Alin Suciu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Cryptology?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Alin Suciu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Data Structures and Algorithms?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Marius Joldoş"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the DataBase Design?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Călin Cenan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the DataBase?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Călin Cenan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Design with Microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Radu Dănescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "Lecturer dr. Mihai"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Development and integration of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Ionuţ Anghel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Specialization didactics?",
    "answer": "Asist. dr. ing. Carmen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Digital Systems Design?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Creţ Octavian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Cristina Pop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Economic law?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof. dr. I swear. Roxana Cordoș"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Physical education and sports?",
    "answer": "As. dr. Suciu Marius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Physical education and sports II?",
    "answer": "As. dr. Suciu Marius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Elaboration of the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor License Project"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Electronic Measurements and Sensors?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Professor Rodica Holonec, Phd eng"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Electrotechnics?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Laura Darabant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the electrical?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Laura Darabant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the English I?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Monica Negoescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the English II?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Monica Negoescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the English Language I (Technical Documents Elaboration)?",
    "answer": "Lecturer dr. Monica Negoescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Fizica?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. Mihai Gabor (series A) Mihai.gabor@phys.utcluj.ro \nConf. dr. Traian Petrișor (series B) Traian.petrisorjr@phys.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Foreign Language II (English - Technical documents elaboration)?",
    "answer": "Assoc.prof. dr. Sanda Paduretu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Formal Languages and Translators?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Anca Mărginean"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof. dr. eng. Radu Răzvan Slăvescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Fundamental Algorithms?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Rodica Potolea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Fundamental Programming Techniques?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Cristina Bianca Pop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German Language I (Technical documents elaboration)?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German Language I?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German Language II (Technical documents elaboration)?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German Language II?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Graduation project defense?",
    "answer": "Diploma project supervisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Graduation project?",
    "answer": "Diploma project supervisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer assisted?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Victor Bâcu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Graphic Processing?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Gorgan Dorian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Image processing?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Florin Oniga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Industrial computer science?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Gheorghe Sebestyen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Information Systems?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Ovidiu Pop – Ovidiu.Pop@cs.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Inginerie software?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Eneia Todoran"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Input/Output Systems and Peripheral Devices?",
    "answer": "Prof. er. eng. Zoltan Francisc Baruch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Instruire Asistata de Calculator (Computer Supported Learning)?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. psycho. Ionuț"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Artificial intelligence?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Anca Mărginean"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Intelligent Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Eng Adrian Groza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Human-calculator interaction?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Tiberiu Mariţa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Knowledge-Based Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Adrian Petru Groza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Economic legislation?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. I swear. Cordoș Roxana Carmen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Limba engleza I?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. Sonia Munteanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the English language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Assoc Sonia Munteanu; Sonia.munteanu@lang.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Limba engleza II?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. Sonia Munteanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the English I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. Sonia Munteanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the French I - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. Adina Forna"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the French language i?",
    "answer": "DR. Anamaria lupan, anamarialupan@yahoo.com"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the French language II - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Lect.dr. Adina Forna, Adina.Forna@lang.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the French II?",
    "answer": "CDA DR. Anamaria lupan, anamarialupan@yahoo.com"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German I.?",
    "answer": "Lect.dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the German II?",
    "answer": "Lect.dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Foreign Language I (German) - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Foreign (German) language - drafting technical documents?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. Mona Tripon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Formal and translator languages?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Anca Mărginean"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Linear Algebra  and Analytical Geometry?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Radu Peter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Logic Design?",
    "answer": "Computer Science and Information Technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Logic programming?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Rodica Potolea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Management and communication?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr. ec. Veronica Maier"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the The management of the student class?",
    "answer": "Education sciences"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Project management?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Mihaela Dînşoreanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Special Mathematics in Engineering?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Ioan Gavrea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Mathematical Analysis I (Differential calculus)?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Dumitru"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Mathematical analysis II (Integral calculus and differential equations)?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Dumitru"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Maintenance of computer systems?",
    "answer": "Ing. Cornel Moisescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Numerical methods?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Ioan Gavrea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Methodology of drafting projects?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Tudor Mureșan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Methodology of project preparation?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Tudor Mureșan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Electronic measurements and sensors?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Radu Munteanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Numerical Methods?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Dumitru"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Object Oriented Programming?",
    "answer": "Lect. dr. eng. Marius Joldoș"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Operating Systems Design?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Adrian Coleşa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Operating Systems?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Adrian Coleşa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Parallel and Distributed Computing?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Anca Hângan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Pattern Recognition Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Sergiu Nedevschi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Pedagogy I (the foundations of pedagogy. Curriculum theory and methodology)?",
    "answer": "Conf. Univ. dr. Liana Crișan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Pedagogy II (training theory and methodology. Theory and methodology of evaluation)?",
    "answer": "Conf. Univ. dr. Liana Crișan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Personal and Professional Development, Ethics and Academic Integrity?",
    "answer": "Lecturer Ph.D. Mihai"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Physical education and sport I / II?",
    "answer": " dr. Suciu Marius Adrian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Physics?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. fiz. Radu Fechete"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practica de domeniu?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Tiberiu Marița"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Specialized practice?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Tiberiu Marița"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practica pedagogica  nivel I licenta?",
    "answer": "Prof. Dr. Ing. Carmen BAL – carmen.bal@dppd.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Pedagogical practice II?",
    "answer": "dr. ing. Iuhos Carmen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practice for the diploma project?",
    "answer": "Diploma project leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practical work for the graduation project?",
    "answer": "Diploma project supervisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practical work in the domain of study?",
    "answer": "Assoc. Prof. dr. eng. Tiberiu Marița"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Practical work in the specialization?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Tiberiu Marita"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Graphic processing?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Dorian Gorgan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Image processing?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Radu Dănescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Functional programming?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Radu Răzvan Slăvescu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Logical programming?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Rodica Potolea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Object -oriented programming?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Raluca Brehar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Programare Web?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Ionuț Anghel – Ionut.Anghel@cs.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Programming in assembly language?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Sebestyén Gheorghe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer programming?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Ion Giosan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Project Protocols and Communications networks?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Emil Cebuc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Design with microprocessors?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Mihai Negru"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the User interface design?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Teodor Ştefănuţ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Logical design?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Octavian Creț"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Proiectare software?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Mihaela Dînşoreanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Date database design?",
    "answer": "Lecturer dr. ing. Călin Cenan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Designing computer networks?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Emil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Designing operating systems?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Adrian Coleșa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Design of numerical systems?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr. ing. Lișman Dragoș"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Design of translators?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Emil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Project Management?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Mihaela Dînșoreanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Project Preparing Methodology?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Tudor Mureșan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Psychology of education?",
    "answer": "Lector dr. Trif Gheorghe Florin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Computer networks?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Vasile Dădârlat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the The security of systems and applications?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr. ing. Marius Joldoș"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Knowledge -based systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Adrian Groza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Quality systems in TI?",
    "answer": "Şl. dr. Anca"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Input/output systems and peripheral equipment?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Zoltan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Sisteme de operare?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Ciprian Oprișa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Forms?",
    "answer": "Șl. dr. ing. Andra Petrovai"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Distributed systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Tudor Cioara"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Sisteme expert?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Radu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Sisteme Informatice Distribuite?",
    "answer": "Șl. dr. ing. Marcel Antal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Sisteme informatice?",
    "answer": "Conf.dr.ing. Ovidiu Pop – Ovidiu.Pop@cs.utcluj.ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Sisteme Inteligente?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Ing Adrian Groza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Software design?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Mihaela Dînșoreanu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Software engineering?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Eneia Todoran"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Special Mathematics I?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Daniela Roșca"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Special Mathematics in engineering?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. Ioan Rasa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the The structure of the calculation systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Gheorghe Sebestyen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Structure of Computer Systems?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Gheorghe Sebestyen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Data structures and algorithms?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Camelia Lemnaru"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Support of diploma project?",
    "answer": "Supervisor License Project"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Systems Theory?",
    "answer": "Assoc.prof. dr. eng. Paula Raica"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Tehnici de Programare Fundamentale?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. ing. Tudor Cioara"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Multimedia technologies?",
    "answer": "Șl. dr. ing. Cornelia Melenti"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Wireless technologies and mobile devices?",
    "answer": "Conf. dr. ing. Adrian Peculea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Systems theory?",
    "answer": "Conf.dr.ing. Paula Raica"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Translator design?",
    "answer": "Assoc. prof. dr. eng. Emil Şefan Chifu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the User Interface Design?",
    "answer": "Prof. dr. eng. Gorgan Dorian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Volunteering 1/3/5/7?",
    "answer": "Volunteer Commission per Faculty"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who teaches the Volunteer 2/4/6/8?",
    "answer": "Volunteer Commission per Faculty"
  }
]